<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>skill on Blog of Kai</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/categories/skill/</link><description>Recent content in skill on Blog of Kai</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 17:16:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/categories/skill/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>《傅雷家书》中对伴侣的理解</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0904/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 17:16:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0904/</guid><description>一九六○年八月二十九日
　亲爱的孩子，八月二十日报告的喜讯使我们心中说不出的欢喜和兴奋。你在人生的旅途中踏上一个新的阶段，开始负起新的责任来，我们要祝贺你，祝福你，鼓励你。希望你拿出像对待音乐艺术一样的毅力、信心、虔诚，来学习人生艺术中最高深的一课。但愿你将来在这一门艺术中得到像你在音乐艺术中一样的成功！发生什么疑难或苦闷，随时向一二个正直而有经验的中、老年人讨教，（你在伦敦已有一年八个月，也该有这样的老成的朋友吧？）深思熟虑，然后决定，切勿单凭一时冲动：只要你能做到这几点，我们也就放
心了。
**对终身伴侣的要求，正如对人生一切的要求一样不能太苛。事情总有正反两面：追得你太迫切了，你觉得负担重，追得不紧了，又觉得不够热烈。温柔的人有时会显得懦弱，刚强了又近于专制。幻想多了未免不切实际，能干的管家太太又觉得俗气。只有长处而没有短处的人在哪儿呢？世界上究竟有没有十全十美的人或事物呢？抚躬自问，自己又完美到什么程度呢？这一类的问题想必你考虑过不止一次。我觉得最主要的还是本质的善良，天性的温厚，开阔的胸襟。有了这三样，其他都可以逐渐培养，而且有了这三样，将来即使遇到大大小小的风波也不致变成悲剧。
做艺术家的妻子比做任何人的妻子都难，你要不预先明白这一点，即使你知道责人太严，责己太宽”，也不容易学会明哲、体贴、容忍。只要能代你解决生活琐事，同时对你的事业感到兴趣就行，对学问的钻研等等暂时不必期望过奢，还得看你们婚后的生活如何。眼前双方先学习相互的尊重、谅解、宽容。
　**对方把你作为她整个的世界固然很危险，但也很宝贵！你既已发觉，一定会慢慢点醒她，最好旁敲侧击而勿正面提出，还要使她感到那是为了维护她的人格独立，扩大她的世界观。**倘若你已经想到奥里维的故事，不妨就把那部书叫她细读一二遍，特别要她注意那一段插曲。像雅葛丽纳那样只知道 love，love，love！的人只是童话中人物，在现实世界中非但得不到love，连日子都会过不下去，因为她除了love一无所知，一无所有，一无所爱。这样狭窄的天地哪像一个天地！这样片面的人生观哪会得到幸福！**无论男女，只有把兴趣集中在事业上，学问上，艺术上，尽量抛开渺小的自我（ego），才有快活的可能，才觉得活得有意义。未经世事的少女往往会存一个荒诞的梦想，以为恋爱时期的感情的高潮也能在婚后维持下去。这是违反自然规律的妄想。古语说，“君子之交谈如水”；又有一句话说，“夫妇相敬如宾”。可见只有平静、含蓄、温和的感情方能持久，另外一句的意义是说，夫妇到后来完全是一种知己朋友的关系，也即是我们所谓的终身伴侣。未婚之前双方能深切领会到这一点。就为将来打定了最可靠的基础，免除了多少不必要的误会和痛苦。
首先态度和心情都要尽可能的冷静。否则观察不会准确。初期交往容易感情冲动，单凭印象，只看见对方的优点，看不出缺点，甚至夸大优点，美化缺点。便是与同性朋友相交也不免如此，对异性更是常有的事。许多青年男女婚前极好，而婚后逐渐相左，甚至反目，往往是这个原因。感情激动时期不仅会耳不聪，目不明，看不清对方，自己也会无意识的只表现好的方面，把缺点隐藏起来。保持冷静还有一个好处，就是不至于为了谈恋爱而荒废正业，或是影响功课或是浪费时间或是损害健康，或是遇到或大或小的波折时扰乱</description></item><item><title>How do I set nudge distance in Illustrator?</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_draw_0623/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 18:33:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_draw_0623/</guid><description>You can change your nudge increments distance in the Preferences Panel(Keyboard increments).</description></item><item><title>MSc Industrial Ecology programme</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_re_0618/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 10:37:22 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_re_0618/</guid><description>Industrial Ecology The MSc Industrial Ecology (joint degree Leiden University and TU Delft) is an interdisciplinary and international programme, which focuses on the analysis of sustainability problems and the design and implementation of solutions for these problems; all from a socio-technical system perspective.</description></item><item><title>Why Was My Paper Rejected without Review?</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_re_0617/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 09:54:35 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_re_0617/</guid><description>A guidance highlighting why your paper was rejected by Environmental Science &amp;amp; Technology and what basic characteristics your paper should possess so it can move forward.</description></item><item><title>Moving the cursor point in word</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0614/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 17:59:34 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0614/</guid><description>The text you type appears wherever the insertion/cursor point is positioned in the current document.</description></item><item><title>How to edit/modify/customise Endnote references styles?</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_re_0613/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 10:28:21 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_re_0613/</guid><description>You will only be able to edit the style if the style is saved to your computer.</description></item><item><title>PhD transferable skills</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_re_0525/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 09:09:10 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_re_0525/</guid><description>Here are examples of PhD skill sets and ways to describe them by University of Michigan.</description></item><item><title>Writing your dissertation - working with your supervisor</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_re_0523/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 11:46:04 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_re_0523/</guid><description>Source
Your supervisor Before you begin your dissertation, it is highly likely you will be assigned a supervisor to oversee your progress from first steps to completion.</description></item><item><title>Changing Fonts in hugo website</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_coder_05172/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_coder_05172/</guid><description>&lt;p>Thanks to Damien. I got new hugo shortcodes for the fonts update in this website.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Make Your Website Social Media Card</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_coder_0517/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_coder_0517/</guid><description>Make Your Website Social Media Card-able on Twitter, Facebook and More See the original link</description></item><item><title>Hugo Figure Shortcode</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_coder_05162/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_coder_05162/</guid><description>Hugo has figure shortcode built-in, so you can easily add figure captions or hyperlink rel attributes to images.</description></item><item><title>Rich Content -- Bult-in Shortcode</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_coder_0516/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_coder_0516/</guid><description>&lt;p>Hugo ships with several &lt;a href="https://gohugo.io/content-management/shortcodes/#use-hugos-built-in-shortcodes">Built-in Shortcodes&lt;/a> for rich content, along with a &lt;a href="https://gohugo.io/about/hugo-and-gdpr/">Privacy Config&lt;/a> and a set of Simple Shortcodes that enable static and no-JS versions of various social media embeds.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_coder_0515/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_coder_0515/</guid><description>&lt;p>This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Math Typesetting</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_coder_0328/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_coder_0328/</guid><description>&lt;p>Mathematical notation in a Hugo project can be enabled by using third party JavaScript libraries.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>