<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Skill on Blogs of Kai</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/categories/skill/</link><description>Recent content in Skill on Blogs of Kai</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 10:40:39 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/categories/skill/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to shoot in Low Light (at night)</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0926/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 10:40:39 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0926/</guid><description>DSLR Tutorial: How to shoot in Low Light (at night) &amp;amp; how to reduce noise! https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AZ9aIB57-Nw
Never go higher than ISO 1600 or the image gets noisy. Keep you shutter speed between1/30s and 1/50s (lights start flickering with higher speed). Aperture should be F/1.2 to F/5.6. Change the contrast of your camera down.</description></item><item><title>Creating multiple subplots using plt.subplots</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0830/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 11:31:15 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0830/</guid><description>pyplot.subplots creates a figure and a grid of subplots with a single call, while providing reasonable control over how the individual plots are created. For more advanced use cases you can use GridSpec for a more general subplot layout or Figure.add_subplot for adding subplots at arbitrary locations within the figure. https://matplotlib.org/stable/gallery/subplots_axes_and_figures/subplots_demo.html
matplotlib.pyplot.subplots matplotlib.pyplot.subplots(nrows=1, ncols=1, *, sharex=False, sharey=False, squeeze=True, subplot_kw=None, gridspec_kw=None, **fig_kw)
Returns: fig: The matplotlib.pyplot.figure object to be used as a container for all the subplots.</description></item><item><title>How do I set nudge distance in Illustrator?</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0623/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 18:33:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0623/</guid><description>You can change your nudge increments distance in the Preferences Panel(Keyboard increments).
Setting nudge distance/keyboard increment Uncheck snap to pixel in the view tab Change the keyboard increment in the Edit tab -&amp;gt;preference from 1 pixel(by fault) to a tiny one which you want. Tip also: the super nudge is a 10-times shift by holding the shift when using the arrow key.</description></item><item><title>MSc Industrial Ecology programme</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0618/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 10:37:22 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0618/</guid><description>Industrial Ecology The MSc Industrial Ecology (joint degree Leiden University and TU Delft) is an interdisciplinary and international programme, which focuses on the analysis of sustainability problems and the design and implementation of solutions for these problems; all from a socio-technical system perspective. The aim of the programme is to educate students to become researchers or practitioners who can contribute to the development of solutions for persistent sustainability problems, such as related to resource depletion and climate change.</description></item><item><title>Why Was My Paper Rejected without Review?</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0617/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 09:54:35 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0617/</guid><description>A guidance highlighting why your paper was rejected by Environmental Science &amp;amp; Technology and what basic characteristics your paper should possess so it can move forward.
(For the original: https://pubs.acs.org/doi/10.1021/acs.est.0c05784)
Highlights:</description></item><item><title>Moving the cursor point in word</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0614/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 17:59:34 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0614/</guid><description>The text you type appears wherever the insertion/cursor point is positioned in the current document. Moving the insertion point around the screen is a critical part of creating and editing documents. To move the insertion point around the screen, you can use either the keyboard or the mouse. Table 1-1 lists ways to move the insertion point by using keystrokes.
https://www.trainingconnection.com/word/lessons/moving-cursor.php
Keystroke Result Up, Down, Left, or Right Arrow Moves the insertion point to the previous or next line or character.</description></item><item><title>How to edit/modify/customise Endnote references styles?</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0613/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 10:28:21 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0613/</guid><description>You will only be able to edit the style if the style is saved to your computer.
Go to Tools - Output styles - select the style to edit. Select Citations to view how the intext citation displays and make any changes. Select Bibliography - Templates to view the templates for the different reference types and make changes. Most of changes would be made in these places.
When you close the style window, you will be prompted to save changes you have made.</description></item><item><title>GIA in the EIOA class: exploring the impact of Brexit (2)</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_06072/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 15:35:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_06072/</guid><description>The Brexit topic from the BBC News.
(The Brexit topic link/Group drive)
Scenario analysis source: Assessing energy and economic impacts of large-scale policy shocks based on Input-Output analysis: Application to Brexit
Research background from the latest Brexit News Farmers should not fear Australia trade deal, UK minister says 27/05/2021 Keywords: free trade deal with Au; competition of UK farmers; gateway to TPP.
Farmers have warned they could struggle to compete if Australia was given tariff-free access to UK markets.</description></item><item><title>GIA in the EIOA class: exploring the impact of Brexit (1)</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0607/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 15:34:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0607/</guid><description>UK companies can and should see the current high-uncertainty environment as a spur to rethink their supply chain strategies and make them more resilient. https://www.mckinsey.com/featured-insights/europe/brexit-the-bigger-picture-rethinking-supply-chains-in-a-time-of-uncertainty
Why Europe is so critical in British supply chains The EU is the UK&amp;rsquo;s largest trading partner, accounting for approximately half of both imports and exports of goods (Exhibit1). Moreover, a large proportion of the UK’s imports from and exports to the EU are in the form of intermediary products—an indicator of the high degree of interconnectedness between UK and EU supply chains (Exhibit 2).</description></item><item><title>PhD transferable skills</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0525/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 09:09:10 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0525/</guid><description>Here are examples of PhD skill sets and ways to describe them by University of Michigan.
Sometimes it's difficult for PhD students to identify what skills they have since the academic experience is not necessarily focused on articulating skill sets. We also often find that PhD students struggle, understandably, to present the transferability of their academic experiences to non-academic contexts. Here are examples of PhD skill sets and ways to describe them.</description></item><item><title>Writing your dissertation - working with your supervisor</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0523/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 11:46:04 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0523/</guid><description>Source
Your supervisor Before you begin your dissertation, it is highly likely you will be assigned a supervisor to oversee your progress from first steps to completion. Your supervisor will help you formulate ideas and give you guidance on how best to develop your research topic and course of action. But you need to always remember that this is your project, and your supervisor will not provide you with content or additional lessons on a particular topic.</description></item><item><title>Changing Fonts in hugo website</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_05172/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_05172/</guid><description>&lt;p>Thanks to Damien. I got new hugo shortcodes for the fonts update in this website.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>EIOA Class: Integrated Group Assignment(IGA)</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_05173/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_05173/</guid><description>&lt;p>Each group is expected to perform a research question about two real-world issues: BREXIT and national stimulus plans.
in a post COVID-19 world.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Make Your Website Social Media Card</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0517/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0517/</guid><description>Make Your Website Social Media Card-able on Twitter, Facebook and More See the original link
We all want our websites to be shared on Twitter, Facebook and all the different channels of social media. Whether they are our own websites that have our blogs and profiles or websites we built for other people. We all value those valuable clicks, so as a means of seduction to make our links clickable, we need to make them look attractive and pretty.</description></item><item><title>Hugo Figure Shortcode</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_05162/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_05162/</guid><description>Hugo has figure shortcode built-in, so you can easily add figure captions or hyperlink rel attributes to images. Documentations can be found here:
https://gohugo.io/content-management/shortcodes/#figure
This theme has 3 CSS classes made for figure elements:
big: images will break the width limit of main content area. left: images will float to the left. right: images will float to the right. If a figure has no class set, the image will behave just like a normal markdown image: !</description></item><item><title>Rich Content -- Bult-in Shortcode</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0516/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0516/</guid><description>&lt;p>Hugo ships with several &lt;a href="https://gohugo.io/content-management/shortcodes/#use-hugos-built-in-shortcodes">Built-in Shortcodes&lt;/a> for rich content, along with a &lt;a href="https://gohugo.io/about/hugo-and-gdpr/">Privacy Config&lt;/a> and a set of Simple Shortcodes that enable static and no-JS versions of various social media embeds.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0515/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0515/</guid><description>&lt;p>This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Math Typesetting</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0328/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0328/</guid><description>&lt;p>Mathematical notation in a Hugo project can be enabled by using third party JavaScript libraries.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>