<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>cml on Blogs of Kai</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/tags/cml/</link><description>Recent content in cml on Blogs of Kai</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 16:37:35 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/tags/cml/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dietary change in high-income nations alone can lead to substantial double climate dividend</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/ioa_dietarychange/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 16:37:35 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/ioa_dietarychange/</guid><description>&lt;p>Published: &lt;strong>10 January 2022&lt;/strong>&lt;br>
&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s43016-021-00431-5">&lt;em>&lt;strong>Nature food&lt;/strong>&lt;/em>&lt;/a>&lt;br>
Zhongxiao Sun $^{1,2}$, Laura Scherer $^{1}$, Arnold Tukker $^{1,3}$, Seth A. Spawn-Lee $^{4,5}$, Martin Bruckner $^{6}$, Holly K. Gibbs $^{4,5}$ &amp;amp; Paul Behrens $^{1,7}$&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The CML Story: How Environmental Sciences Entered the Debate on LCA</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/re_12272/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 11:59:33 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/re_12272/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://core.ac.uk/download/pdf/159147033.pdf">&lt;em>&lt;strong>The International Journal of Life Cycle Assessment&lt;/strong>&lt;/em>&lt;/a>&lt;br>
Published: &lt;strong>December 1997&lt;/strong>&lt;br>
&lt;strong>Heinz Gabathuler&lt;/strong>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>LC-IMPACT: A regionalized life cycle damage assessment method</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/re_0818/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 12:19:10 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/re_0818/</guid><description>https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1111/jiec.13018
Abstract Here, we present the LC-IMPACT method that provides characterization factors at the damage level for 11 impact categories related to three areas of protection (human health, ecosystem quality, natural resources).</description></item><item><title>Advanced Course on LCA —— Session 3: Economic Allocation</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/re_0816/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 16:13:31 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/re_0816/</guid><description>Session 3 Purpose This software session focuses on reproducing the results of an LCA paper on economic allocation, defining functional flows and identifying multi functional processes, with the software program CMLCA. In today’s exercises, you will learn:
to understand the main principles of economic allocation; how such analyses work in CMLCA software. You may perform the exercise alone or together with (a) colleague(s) in a virtual room, and again, you don’t have to hand in the results.</description></item><item><title>Economic Allocation: Examples and Derived Decision Tree</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/lca_econalloc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 09:24:52 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/lca_econalloc/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/BF02978533">The International Journal of Life Cycle Assessment volume&lt;/a>&lt;br>
Jeroen B. Guinde*, Reinout Heijungs and Gjah Huppes&lt;br>
2004&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Proper or messy allocation?--Systematic approach to identifying and solving multi-functionality in LCA</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/re_0814/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2021 11:20:07 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/re_0814/</guid><description>Avoided burden1
Most existing LCA databases today do not include multi-functional processes.
including ecoinvent MF is &amp;lsquo;solved&amp;rsquo; by database developers by delivering only mono-functional datasets.
Mostly, practitioners cannot change this methodological decision anymore and often don&amp;rsquo;t realize that they are handling (&amp;lsquo;accepting&amp;rsquo;) more MF issues than they realize.
Consequently, most software doesn&amp;rsquo;t include ways to address MF.
While it is known as one of the most determining factors of LCA results.</description></item><item><title>Waste is not a service</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/re_0808/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2021 11:03:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/re_0808/</guid><description>https://link.springer.com/content/pdf/10.1007/s11367-021-01955-5.pdf
Almost every overview of LCA gives a graphical indication of the idea of a life cycle. Such diagrams consist of a linear sequence or network of blocks, connected with arrows, representing the major life stages of a product life cycle. Examples from recent textbooks on LCA can be found in Klöpffer and Grahl (2014, p. 2), Jolliet et al. (2016, p. 36), and Hauschild et al. (2018, p. 120). All such flow diagrams agree on the basic setup of a chronological order: resource becomes products, products are used, and it all ends with disposal of waste.</description></item><item><title>GIA in the EIOA class: exploring the impact of Brexit (2)</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill/skill_06072/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 15:35:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill/skill_06072/</guid><description>The Brexit topic from the BBC News.
(The Brexit topic link/Group drive)
Scenario analysis source: Assessing energy and economic impacts of large-scale policy shocks based on Input-Output analysis: Application to Brexit
Research background from the latest Brexit News Farmers should not fear Australia trade deal, UK minister says 27/05/2021
Keywords: free trade deal with Au; competition of UK farmers; gateway to TPP.
Farmers have warned they could struggle to compete if Australia was given tariff-free access to UK markets.</description></item><item><title>GIA in the EIOA class: exploring the impact of Brexit (1)</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill/skill_0607/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 15:34:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill/skill_0607/</guid><description>UK companies can and should see the current high-uncertainty environment as a spur to rethink their supply chain strategies and make them more resilient.
https://www.mckinsey.com/featured-insights/europe/brexit-the-bigger-picture-rethinking-supply-chains-in-a-time-of-uncertainty
Why Europe is so critical in British supply chains The EU is the UK&amp;rsquo;s largest trading partner, accounting for approximately half of both imports and exports of goods (Exhibit1). Moreover, a large proportion of the UK’s imports from and exports to the EU are in the form of intermediary products—an indicator of the high degree of interconnectedness between UK and EU supply chains (Exhibit 2).</description></item><item><title>EIOA Class: Integrated Group Assignment(IGA)</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill/skill_05173/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill/skill_05173/</guid><description>&lt;p>Each group is expected to perform a research question about two real-world issues: BREXIT and national stimulus plans.&lt;br>
in a post COVID-19 world.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>