<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Daily English on Blogs of Kai</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/categories/daily-english/</link><description>Recent content in Daily English on Blogs of Kai</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 09:59:05 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/categories/daily-english/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cappuccino vs. Latte vs. Macchiato - What's the Difference?</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_1108/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 09:59:05 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_1108/</guid><description>&lt;p>If you’re exploring the world of milk-based espresso drinks, you may be confused. Almost everyone knows what a Cappuccino is, but what the heck is a Macchiato? and what about a Latte?&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>14 Differences Between the Girl you Date and the Woman you Marry</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_1105/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2021 21:48:02 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_1105/</guid><description/></item><item><title>The Maillard Reaction Turns 100</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_1026/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 11:25:40 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_1026/</guid><description>&lt;p>Scientists celebrate the centennial of a reaction that makes cooked food tasty, but also produces worrisome molecules in our meals and bodies.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>What happens when we cook food? Understanding acrylamide formation</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_10262/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 11:25:40 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_10262/</guid><description>&lt;p>The process of heating can also lead to the formation of less favourable substances. One such compound that has received much scientific and media interest over recent years is acrylamide.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>What is the healthiest way to cook vegetables to maximize their nutritional value?</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_1025/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 21:47:53 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_1025/</guid><description>&lt;p>Vegetables lose some nutritional value in transportation, so when possible, buy produce from farmers’ markets.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>8 Ways To Create Flow According to Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0927/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 10:41:11 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0927/</guid><description>Want to increase your well-being, creativity, and productivity?
If so, you might want to cultivate flow, a concept describing those moments when you’re completely absorbed in a challenging but doable task.
Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi, considered one of the co-founders of positive psychology, was the first to identify and research flow. (If you’re not sure how to pronounce his name, here’s a phonetic guide: “Me high? Cheeks send me high!”)
“The best moments in our lives are not the passive, receptive, relaxing times .</description></item><item><title>'They would have let Hitler buy ads': Sacha Baron Cohen's scathing attack on Facebook</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0830/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 19:46:17 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0830/</guid><description>Sacha Baron Cohen denounces Facebook, Twitter, YouTube and Google as &amp;lsquo;the greatest propaganda machine in history&amp;rsquo; and culpable for a surge in &amp;lsquo;murderous attacks on religious and ethnic minorities&amp;rsquo;. The actor focuses on Facebook, saying that &amp;lsquo;if you pay them, the platform will run any &amp;ldquo;political&amp;rdquo; ad you want, even if it&amp;rsquo;s a lie&amp;rsquo;. Baron Cohen is speaking on Thursday at Never Is Now, the Anti-Defamation League’s summit on antisemitism and hate in New York, where he is presented with the organisation’s international leadership award.</description></item><item><title>The Shortest History of Europe</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0827/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 19:09:58 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0827/</guid><description>CHAPTER 1. Europe Classical and Medieval1 EUROPEAN CIVILISATION IS UNIQUE because it is the only civilisation which has imposed itself on the rest of the world. It did this by conquest and settlement; by its economic power; by the power of its ideas; and because it had things that everyone else wanted. Today every country on earth uses the discoveries of science and the technologies that flow from it, and science was a European invention.</description></item><item><title>Dutch Golden Age: Crash Course European History</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0815/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 21:29:57 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0815/</guid><description>The Dutch Golden Age was a period in the history of the Netherlands, roughly spanning the era from 1588 (the birth of the Dutch Republic) to 1672 (the Rampjaar, &amp;ldquo;Disaster Year&amp;rdquo;), in which Dutch trade, science, and art and the Dutch military were among the most acclaimed in the world. The first section is characterized by the Eighty Years' War, which ended in 1648. The Golden Age continued in peacetime during the Dutch Republic until the end of the century, when costly conflicts, including the Franco-Dutch War and War of the Spanish Succession fuelled economic decline.</description></item><item><title>Love handles: What causes them, and how do you get rid of them?</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0725/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 14:42:10 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0725/</guid><description>https://www.healthline.com/health/what-causes-love-handles
What are love handles? &amp;ldquo;Love handles&amp;rdquo; are areas of skin that extend outward from the hips. When combined with tight clothing, love handles become more pronounced, but they aren&amp;rsquo;t caused by tight clothing alone. They indicate excess fat accumulation around the hips and abdominal area.
What causes love handles?
The underlying cause of love handles is fat retention.
Generally speaking, fat cells accumulate when your body takes in too many calories or you don&amp;rsquo;t burn as many calories as you&amp;rsquo;re consuming.</description></item><item><title>30 Tough but Very Important Advanced Verbs for Daily Use</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0721/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2021 20:09:18 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0721/</guid><description>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WGce2fBK0aM&amp;amp;t=768s
to accomplish
to succeed in doing something, especially after trying very hard
= achieve
Mission accomplished.
Try to accomplish your aim with diligence.
to accumulate
to gradually get more and more money, possessions, knowledge etc over a period of time
eg. Capitalism is not just about accumulation.
In everyday English, people usually say build up rather than accumulate.
to be beware
used to warn someone to be careful because something is dangerous</description></item><item><title>Of Studies</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0718/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2021 12:15:36 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0718/</guid><description>Of Studies by Francis Bacon (1625)
Studies serve for delight, for ornament1, and for ability. Their chief use for delight is in privateness and retiring; for ornament, is in discourse; and for ability, is in the judgment and disposition of business. For expert men can execute, and perhaps judge of particulars2, one by one; but the general counseles, and the plots and marshalling of affairs, come best from those that learned.</description></item><item><title>Weather</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0717/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jul 2021 15:05:14 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0717/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Wherever you go, no matter what the weather, always bring your own sunshine.&amp;rdquo; Anthony J. D&amp;rsquo;Angelo.
Cards It&amp;rsquo;s great here. Have had unbroken sunshine ever since we arrived. We&amp;rsquo;re having a wonderful time-though in the middle of the day it&amp;rsquo;s just too scorching hot to do anything but lie on the beach soaking up the sunshine. This is the life!
It&amp;rsquo;s been pouring with rain all day. In fact I&amp;rsquo;ve never seen such torrential rain!</description></item><item><title>Special issue of Euro 2020: England vs Italy</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0712/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 09:24:55 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0712/</guid><description>Live blogs From MARCE and EURO 2020 offical.
Minute 1: Kick off in the Euro 2020 final!
Here we go then! In the rainy conditions, Italy vs England kicks off. It&amp;rsquo;s the Euro 2020 final. Let&amp;rsquo;s see who replaces Portugal to become the champions of Europe.
Minute 2: England go ahead already!
England take a very early lead in this Euro 2020 final, launching a counter attack from an Italian corner.</description></item><item><title>7 Things Tolkien Said About Life 7 Things Tolkien Said About Life — 7 Comments</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0710/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 22:42:15 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0710/</guid><description>J.R.R. Tolkien wrote many books, including the Middle-earth stories. He is particularly known for The Lord of the Rings and like many stories of an epic journey, LOTR lets us take away lessons we can apply to our life.
No matter how surreal his epic stories are, the pieces of wisdom reflected in them mirror that of the wisdom we must gain to champion our life here on earth.
7 Things Tolkien Said About Life</description></item><item><title>Have/Get/Make/Let—Learn when to use causative verbs.</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0703/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 09:52:27 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0703/</guid><description>LET = Permit Something To Happen I don’t let my kids watch violent movies.
Mary’s father won’t let her adopt a puppy because he’s allergic to dogs.
Our boss doesn’t let us eat lunch at our desks; we have to eat in the cafeteria.
Oops! I wasn’t paying attention while cooking, and I let the food burn.
Don’t let the advertising expenses surpass $1000.
MAKE = Force Or Require Someone To Take An Action My ex-boyfriend loved sci-fi and made me watch every episode of his favorite show.</description></item><item><title>Is beer better (or worse) for you than wine?</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0627/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 23:34:41 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0627/</guid><description>Few drinks (save tea or coffee) divide the world so spectacularly as beer or wine. There’s no accounting for taste, of course – but there are subtle differences in the way they affect your body and determine your health. Is one more fattening than another? How do their heart benefits compare? And which gives the worse hangover?
BBC Future has combed through the data to bust some of the myths surrounding two of the world’s favourite drinks.</description></item><item><title>What you should know about beer?</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0626/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 21:50:46 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0626/</guid><description>BEER: WHERE DO ALL THOSE FLAVOURS COME FROM? There are thousands of different ways that yeast, malt, and hops that can be combined to make beer, and all those combinations can lead to lots of interesting outcomes. There are also a LOT of additives you can put in beer to give it different flavours, but I’m going to focus on the core ingredients: yeast, hops, and malt.
Yeast Yeast is a fungus.</description></item><item><title>Alternative words and humour</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0612/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 22:25:16 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0612/</guid><description>Some alternatives for please, sorry, fine, sad, tired and bored.
Alternatives for please Would you mind&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;d appreciate it if you could&amp;hellip; Would you be able to &amp;hellip; I wonder if you might&amp;hellip; Alernatives for sorry It was thoughtless of me&amp;hellip; It was careless of me&amp;hellip; I owe you a pology for my awful behaviour. I take full responsibility for my actions. I sincerely apologise. For I&amp;rsquo;m fine (I) couldn&amp;rsquo;t be better!</description></item><item><title>First run with Garmin forerunner 245</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0609/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 18:13:24 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0609/</guid><description>Not to be so professional and just for the recording of every running exercise in Leiden I chose the plain and runner-designed Garmin forerunner 245.
Plenty of choice at Garmin Garmin is working hard in the field of wearables. In recent years, the American company has successfully shifted its focus from navigation boxes for the car to GPS-based sports watches and bicycle computers. In the first quarter of this year, Garmin was number three worldwide in terms of numbers of smartwatches sold, with only Samsung and Apple to tolerate.</description></item><item><title>Feel struggling to response 'How are you'</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0607/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 20:40:07 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0607/</guid><description>Since I&amp;rsquo;m here I couldn&amp;rsquo;t count that how many times people asking me &amp;lsquo;how are you&amp;rsquo; and I actually don&amp;rsquo;t know how to response this due to the difference of the greeting ways.
Today I came across Grace in the corridor of our apartment building. Again I was asking &amp;lsquo;How are you?&amp;rsquo; It could be simple as a normal greeting way here but I just not be adapted to it. At the hometown we just say people&amp;rsquo;s name if he/she is an acquaintance.</description></item><item><title>All about the lettuce</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0602/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 18:46:44 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0602/</guid><description>&amp;lsquo;Leaf lettuce, head lettuce, green lettuce, red lettuce….who knew there were so many kinds of lettuce? This is your handy guide to knowing what kind of lettuce your are eating with.&amp;rsquo;
Types of Lettuce Iceberg Butterhead Romaine Leaf Kale ICEBERG LETTUCE This is probably the most famous and recognizable form of head lettuce. Iceberg lettuce is also sometimes referred to as crisphead, and it is a pale green leafy vegetable that forms into a tight cabbage style head.</description></item><item><title>9 Everyday verbs 3</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0526/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 09:02:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0526/</guid><description>Have Take Break smash verb [transitive] to break something with a lot of force
A policeman smashed his camera.
snap verb [transitive] to break something into two pieces, making a loud noise – used especially about long thin objects
He snapped the sticks in two.
split verb [transitive] to separate something into two pieces along a straight line
Using a sharp knife, split the melon in half.</description></item><item><title>8 Everyday verbs 2</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0524/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 20:24:10 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0524/</guid><description>Get is a very common verb in English, but it is not always appropriate for talking about changes. Note
also alternatives to get which can improve your style.
Go, not get People go mad/bald/grey/blind/deaf. Go is often used for sudden, usually negative, changes:
He was very embarrassed and his face went red. Go can also be used for slower colour changes:
The pages of the book had gone yellow over the years.</description></item><item><title>Covid 19 Self Testing</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0518/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 22:07:22 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0518/</guid><description>Interesting warnings These kits are only designed for human use．
Use a separate test kit for each person. You can only use each item in　the test kit once. Do not re-use the items．
Do not eat or drink for at least 30 minutes before doing the test to
reduce the risk of spoiling the test.
What you need to do Prepare your test area and check your test kit contents Set up your test Take your swab sample Process the swab sample Read your result Report your result Safely dispose of your test kit Store the test kit at room temperature or in a cool dry place (2°C</description></item></channel></rss>