<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Spatially Explicit Input–Output Analysis on Blogs of Kai</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/categories/spatially-explicit-inputoutput-analysis/</link><description>Recent content in Spatially Explicit Input–Output Analysis on Blogs of Kai</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 10:10:29 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/categories/spatially-explicit-inputoutput-analysis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>From Satellite to Supply Chain: New Approaches Connect Earth Observation to Economic Decisions</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0710/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 10:10:29 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0710/</guid><description>why we need more transparent supply chains? A growing share of countries’ environmental and social impacts occurs abroad; Businesses and shareholders need to identify and evaluate the potential environmental impacts and biodiversity loss of their foreign producers; Individual consumers increasingly ask for the locations and magnitude of the impacts associated with their choices; Contributing to an accountability framework that would trigger higher environmental standards in the specific industry of producing countries.</description></item><item><title>Linking Global Crop and Livestock Consumption to Local Production Hotspots</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0606/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 09:42:03 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0606/</guid><description>Identifying production hotspots for global crop and livestock consumption by a Spatially Explicit Multi-Reginal Input-Output model ( Zhongxiao&amp;rsquo;s work on Global Food Security).
Keywords: primary crops; animal husbandry; spatially explicit; Multi-Regional Input-Output(MRIO) analysis.
Research background Food security is challenged by increasing global food demand driven by population growth and animal-based diets. More crop production requires increasing areas of land and fresh water, causing associated environmental impacts1. Also livestock should be a focus as their feed contains harmful ingredients2 which will released to our environment finally.</description></item></channel></rss>