<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Code on Blogs of Kai</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/categories/code/</link><description>Recent content in Code on Blogs of Kai</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 17:47:11 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/categories/code/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How effectively delete and add a git submodule</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_1017/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 17:47:11 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_1017/</guid><description>&lt;p>Git Submodules are the concept related to modularity. One git repository can be added to another as a submodule and maintained separately. Instead of being tightly coupled, it is loosely coupled and is easy to maintain.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Customizing Figure Layouts Using GridSpec and Other Functions</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0901/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 12:16:46 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0901/</guid><description>https://matplotlib.org/stable/tutorials/intermediate/gridspec.html#sphx-glr-tutorials-intermediate-gridspec-py</description></item><item><title>4 data structures in Python</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0831/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 12:08:51 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0831/</guid><description>Tuple Tuples are used to store multiple items in a single variable. A tuple is a collection which is ordered and unchangeable. Tuples are written with round brackets.
thistuple = (&amp;quot;apple&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;banana&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;cherry&amp;quot;) Tuple items are ordered, unchangeable, and allow duplicate values. When we say that tuples are ordered, it means that the items have a defined order, and that order will not change. Tuples are unchangeable, meaning that we cannot change, add or remove items after the tuple has been created.</description></item><item><title>Changing Fonts in hugo website</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_05172/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_05172/</guid><description>&lt;p>Thanks to Damien. I got new hugo shortcodes for the fonts update in this website.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Make Your Website Social Media Card</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0517/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0517/</guid><description>Make Your Website Social Media Card-able on Twitter, Facebook and More See the original link
We all want our websites to be shared on Twitter, Facebook and all the different channels of social media. Whether they are our own websites that have our blogs and profiles or websites we built for other people. We all value those valuable clicks, so as a means of seduction to make our links clickable, we need to make them look attractive and pretty.</description></item><item><title>Hugo Figure Shortcode</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_05162/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_05162/</guid><description>Hugo has figure shortcode built-in, so you can easily add figure captions or hyperlink rel attributes to images. Documentations can be found here:
https://gohugo.io/content-management/shortcodes/#figure
This theme has 3 CSS classes made for figure elements:
big: images will break the width limit of main content area. left: images will float to the left. right: images will float to the right. If a figure has no class set, the image will behave just like a normal markdown image: !</description></item><item><title>Rich Content -- Bult-in Shortcode</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0516/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0516/</guid><description>&lt;p>Hugo ships with several &lt;a href="https://gohugo.io/content-management/shortcodes/#use-hugos-built-in-shortcodes">Built-in Shortcodes&lt;/a> for rich content, along with a &lt;a href="https://gohugo.io/about/hugo-and-gdpr/">Privacy Config&lt;/a> and a set of Simple Shortcodes that enable static and no-JS versions of various social media embeds.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0515/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0515/</guid><description>&lt;p>This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Math Typesetting</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0328/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0328/</guid><description>&lt;p>Mathematical notation in a Hugo project can be enabled by using third party JavaScript libraries.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>