<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>health on Blogs of Kai</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/tags/health/</link><description>Recent content in health on Blogs of Kai</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 14:42:10 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/tags/health/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Love handles: What causes them, and how do you get rid of them?</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/english/post/de_0725/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 14:42:10 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/english/post/de_0725/</guid><description>https://www.healthline.com/health/what-causes-love-handles
What are love handles? &amp;ldquo;Love handles&amp;rdquo; are areas of skin that extend outward from the hips. When combined with tight clothing, love handles become more pronounced, but they aren&amp;rsquo;t caused by tight clothing alone. They indicate excess fat accumulation around the hips and abdominal area.
What causes love handles?
The underlying cause of love handles is fat retention.
Generally speaking, fat cells accumulate when your body takes in too many calories or you don&amp;rsquo;t burn as many calories as you&amp;rsquo;re consuming.</description></item><item><title>Is beer better (or worse) for you than wine?</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/english/post/de_0627/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 23:34:41 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/english/post/de_0627/</guid><description>Few drinks (save tea or coffee) divide the world so spectacularly as beer or wine. There’s no accounting for taste, of course – but there are subtle differences in the way they affect your body and determine your health. Is one more fattening than another? How do their heart benefits compare? And which gives the worse hangover?
BBC Future has combed through the data to bust some of the myths surrounding two of the world’s favourite drinks.</description></item><item><title>Covid 19 Self Testing</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/english/post/life_health_0518/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 22:07:22 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/english/post/life_health_0518/</guid><description>Interesting warnings British humour? These kits are only designed for human use． Use a separate test kit for each person. You can only use each item in　the test kit once. Do not re-use the items．
Do not eat or drink for at least 30 minutes before doing the test to reduce the risk of spoiling the test.
What you need to do Prepare your test area and check your test kit contents Set up your test Take your swab sample Process the swab sample Read your result Report your result Safely dispose of your test kit Store the test kit at room temperature or in a cool dry place (2°C to 30°C).</description></item></channel></rss>