<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>GIS on Blogs of Kai</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/tags/gis/</link><description>Recent content in GIS on Blogs of Kai</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 09:16:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/tags/gis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A combined GIS-archetype approach to model residential space heating energy: A case study for the Netherlands including validation</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_1110/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 09:16:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_1110/</guid><description>&lt;p>A transferable residential space heating energy model is developed based on geo-referenced data and archetypes.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Emerging role of Geographical Information System (GIS), Life Cycle Assessment (LCA) and spatial LCA (GIS-LCA) in sustainable bioenergy planning</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0822/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2021 22:00:18 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0822/</guid><description>https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0960852417303516#f0010
Abstract Sustainability of a bioenergy project depends on precise assessment of biomass resource, planning of cost-effective logistics and evaluation of possible environmental implications. In this context, this paper reviews the role and applications of geo-spatial tool such as Geographical Information System (GIS) for precise agro-residue resource assessment, biomass logistic and power plant design. Further, application of Life Cycle Assessment (LCA) in understanding the potential impact of agro-residue bioenergy generation on different ecosystem services has also been reviewed and limitations associated with LCA variability and uncertainty were discussed.</description></item><item><title>Mapping global patterns of land use decision-making</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0630/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 11:01:39 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0630/</guid><description>ŽigaMalekaPeter H.Verburgab
Department of Environmental Geography, Institute for Environmental Studies (IVM), Vrije Universiteit Amsterdam, De Boelelaan 1087, 1081 HV Amsterdam, The Netherlands
Available online 23 September 2020.
How such local-scale patterns of decision-making can be used to explain land-use change globally is unknown. Using a collection of local studies from a literature review, we studied the contextual conditions of different modes of land-use change decision-making and present global maps of the potential distribution of decision-making in land-use change.</description></item></channel></rss>