<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>manual on Blogs of Kai</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/tags/manual/</link><description>Recent content in manual on Blogs of Kai</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 18:13:24 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/tags/manual/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>First run with Garmin forerunner 245</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/life_sport_0609/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 18:13:24 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/life_sport_0609/</guid><description>Not to be so professional and just for the recording of every running exercise in Leiden I chose the plain and runner-designed Garmin forerunner 245.
Plenty of choice at Garmin Garmin is working hard in the field of wearables. In recent years, the American company has successfully shifted its focus from navigation boxes for the car to GPS-based sports watches and bicycle computers. In the first quarter of this year, Garmin was number three worldwide in terms of numbers of smartwatches sold, with only Samsung and Apple to tolerate.</description></item><item><title>Covid 19 Self Testing</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/life_health_0518/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 22:07:22 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/life_health_0518/</guid><description>Interesting warnings British humour? These kits are only designed for human use． Use a separate test kit for each person. You can only use each item in　the test kit once. Do not re-use the items．
Do not eat or drink for at least 30 minutes before doing the test to reduce the risk of spoiling the test.
What you need to do Prepare your test area and check your test kit contents Set up your test Take your swab sample Process the swab sample Read your result Report your result Safely dispose of your test kit Store the test kit at room temperature or in a cool dry place (2°C to 30°C).</description></item></channel></rss>