<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>land use on Blogs of Kai</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/tags/land-use/</link><description>Recent content in land use on Blogs of Kai</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 09:25:01 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/tags/land-use/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Nature-based-solutions--Scenarios for the Global Land Outlook 2</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/english/post/re_0817/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 09:25:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/english/post/re_0817/</guid><description>This study quantifies the potential effects of land restoration for soil, food, water, biodiversity and climate change at the global and regional levels, using three global land-use scenarios up to 2050.
https://www.pbl.nl/en/publications/the-global-potential-for-land-restoration-scenarios-for-the-global-land-outlook-2
https://www.pbl.nl/sites/default/files/downloads/pbl-2021-the-global-potential-for-land-restoration-glo2-3898.pdf
https://themasites.pbl.nl/nature-based-solutions/nature-based-solutions
Nature-based solutions and scenarios Nature-based Solutions (BbS) are actions that enable the protection, sustainable management and restoration of natural and managed ecosystems, that can simultaneously provide human well-being an biodiversity benefits.
Nature-based solutions (NbS) include restoration, management, and rehabilitation measures, as well as conservation of ecosystems, that enhance nature’s contribution to people, such as agroforestry, conservation agriculture, assisted natural regeneration and urban green and blue spaces.</description></item><item><title>Land use indicators in LCA</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/english/post/re_rp_0810/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 09:54:21 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/english/post/re_rp_0810/</guid><description>Principles for life cycle inventories of land use on a global scale Thomas Koellner, Laura de Baan, Tabea Beck, Miguel Brandão, Barbara Civit, Mark Goedkoop, Manuele Margni, Llorenç Milà i Canals, Ruedi Müller-Wenk, Bo Weidema &amp;amp; Bastian Wittstock The International Journal of Life Cycle Assessment volume 18, pages1203–1215 (2013) https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s11367-012-0392-0
Land use elementary flows In LCA, land occupation and land transformation can be distinguished as basic types of land use elementary flows (Milà i Canals et al.</description></item><item><title>Literature review on the land use of future energy</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/english/post/re_rp_0809/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 11:26:59 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/english/post/re_rp_0809/</guid><description>https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S1364032108001354
Land use and electricity generation: A life-cycle analysis Renewable and Sustainable Energy Reviews Volume 13, Issues 6–7, August–September 2009, Pages 1465-1474
Vasilis Fthenakis¹, Hyung Chul Kim² ¹ National Photovoltaic Environmental Research Center, Brookhaven National Laboratory, Bldg 475B, Upton, NY 11973, United States ² Center for Life Cycle Analysis, Columbia University, New York, NY 10027, United States
Abstract Renewable-energy sources often are regarded as dispersed and difficult to collect, thus requiring substantial land resources in comparison to conventional energy sources.</description></item><item><title>Mapping global patterns of land use decision-making</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/english/post/re_0630/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 11:01:39 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/english/post/re_0630/</guid><description>ŽigaMalekaPeter H.Verburgab Department of Environmental Geography, Institute for Environmental Studies (IVM), Vrije Universiteit Amsterdam, De Boelelaan 1087, 1081 HV Amsterdam, The Netherlands Available online 23 September 2020.
How such local-scale patterns of decision-making can be used to explain land-use change globally is unknown. Using a collection of local studies from a literature review, we studied the contextual conditions of different modes of land-use change decision-making and present global maps of the potential distribution of decision-making in land-use change.</description></item></channel></rss>