<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Economics on Blogs of Kai</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/categories/economics/</link><description>Recent content in Economics on Blogs of Kai</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 10:55:53 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/categories/economics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CBAM needs universal adoption of methods for measuring carbon intensity</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_1012/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 10:55:53 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_1012/</guid><description>August 31, 2021 by Dolf Gielen, Massamba Thioye and Francisco Boshell Leave a Comment. https://energypost.eu/cbam-needs-universal-adoption-of-methods-for-measuring-carbon-intensity/
Europe needs to account for the emissions of imported goods. That cannot happen without the international agreement on standards and certification systems for the carbon intensity of all steps in the value chain for all relevant products. Dolf Gielen and Francisco Boshell at IRENA and Massamba Thioye at the UNFCCC explain that several such systems exist around the world, but they need to be harmonised and widely adopted to truly reflect what is happening.</description></item><item><title>Distributional impacts of carbon pricing in developing Asia</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0924/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 11:11:07 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0924/</guid><description>Distributional impacts of carbon pricing in developing Asia Jan C. Steckel, Ira I. Dorband, Lorenzo Montrone, Hauke Ward, Leonard Missbach, Fabian Hafner, Michael Jakob &amp;amp; Sebastian Renner Nature Sustainability (2021) Published: 23 September 2021 Mercator Research Institute on Global Commons and Climate Change, Berlin, Germany Department Economics of Climate Change, Technische Universität Berlin, Berlin, Germany https://www.nature.com/articles/s41893-021-00758-8
Abstract Understanding who would be affected in which way by carbon pricing is pivotal for effective and socially equitable policy design, addressing climate change and reducing inequality.</description></item></channel></rss>