<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Economics on Blogs of Kai</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/categories/economics/</link><description>Recent content in Economics on Blogs of Kai</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 12:37:10 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/categories/economics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Future scenarios of global plastic waste generation and disposal</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/pl/eco_futureglobalplasticwastegenerationanddisposal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 12:37:10 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/pl/eco_futureglobalplasticwastegenerationanddisposal/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41599-018-0212-7#Sec2">&lt;em>&lt;strong>Nature humanities and social sciences communications&lt;/strong>&lt;/em>&lt;/a>&lt;br>
Published: &lt;strong>29 January 2019&lt;/strong>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Predicted growth in plastic waste exceeds efforts to mitigate plastic pollution</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/pl/eco_predictedgrowth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 12:19:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/pl/eco_predictedgrowth/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.science.org/doi/10.1126/science.aba3656#con2">&lt;em>&lt;strong>Science&lt;/strong>&lt;/em>&lt;/a>&lt;br>
Received:7 January 2020; Accepted:4 August 2020; Published in print:&lt;strong>18 September 2020&lt;/strong>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Energy system decarbonization and productivity gains reduced the coupling of CO2 emissions and economic growth in 73 countries between 1970 and 2016</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/econ_ranran/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 21:28:41 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/econ_ranran/</guid><description/></item><item><title>When Should I Use Confidence Intervals, Prediction Intervals, and Tolerance Intervals</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/econ_re1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 22:54:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/econ_re1/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Four Tips on How to Perform a Regression Analysis that Avoids Common Problems</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/econ_re2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 22:52:40 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/econ_re2/</guid><description>&lt;p>This blog presents four tips that will help you avoid the more common mistakes of &lt;strong>applied regression analysis&lt;/strong> that I identified in the research literature.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Regression Analysis Tutorial and Examples</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/econ_re3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 22:48:43 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/econ_re3/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Multiple Regression Analysis: Use Adjusted R-Squared and Predicted R-Squared to Include the Correct Number of Variables</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/econ_re4/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 17:44:19 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/econ_re4/</guid><description>&lt;p>This blog looks at why you should resist the urge to add too many predictors to a regression model, and how the adjusted R-squared and predicted R-squared can help!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>R-squared Shrinkage and Power and Sample Size Guidelines for Regression Analysis</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/econ_re5/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 16:57:20 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/econ_re5/</guid><description>&lt;p>This blog looks at how to obtain an unbiased and reasonably precise estimate of the population R-squared. It also presents power and sample size guidelines for regression analysis.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The memory of expected value and variance</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/econ_re6/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 12:41:56 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/econ_re6/</guid><description>&lt;p>Reviewing the basic statistical concepts: expected value and variance.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Regression analysis: How do I interpret R-squared and assess the Goodness-of-Fit?</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/econ_re7/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 12:05:35 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/econ_re7/</guid><description>&lt;p>Low R-squared values are not always bad and high R-squared values are not always good!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How to Interpret a Regression Model with Low R-squared and Low P values</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/econ_re8/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 10:33:17 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/econ_re8/</guid><description>&lt;p>What if your regression model has significant variables but explains little of the variability? With low P values and a low R-squared.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Integrated assessment modelling (IAM)</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/econ_iam/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 10:37:24 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/econ_iam/</guid><description>&lt;p>A type of scientific modelling that tries to link main features of society and economy with the biosphere and atmosphere into one modelling framework.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>OECD Expert workshop on Economic Modelling of Climate and Related Tipping Points</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/econ_tippingp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 19:45:49 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/econ_tippingp/</guid><description>&lt;p>Emerging evidence highlights the increasing risks of &lt;em>&lt;strong>non-linearities and systemic changes caused by climate change&lt;/strong>&lt;/em>. These include large-scale tipping points in the earth’s climate such as the disintegration of the Greenland and West Antarctic Ice Sheets, permafrost collapse, and the breakdown of the Atlantic Meridional Overturning Circulation among others.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Complexity Economics</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/econ_complexity/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 16:05:34 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/econ_complexity/</guid><description>&lt;p>From &lt;strong>The Institute for New Economic Thinking at the Oxford Martin School (INET Oxford)&lt;/strong>&lt;br>
&lt;a href="https://www.inet.ox.ac.uk/research/programmes/complexity-economics/">https://www.inet.ox.ac.uk/research/programmes/complexity-economics/&lt;/a>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>CBAM needs universal adoption of methods for measuring carbon intensity</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/econ_cbam/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 10:55:53 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/econ_cbam/</guid><description>August 31, 2021 by Dolf Gielen, Massamba Thioye and Francisco Boshell Leave a Comment.
https://energypost.eu/cbam-needs-universal-adoption-of-methods-for-measuring-carbon-intensity/
Europe needs to account for the emissions of imported goods. That cannot happen without the international agreement on standards and certification systems for the carbon intensity of all steps in the value chain for all relevant products. Dolf Gielen and Francisco Boshell at IRENA and Massamba Thioye at the UNFCCC explain that several such systems exist around the world, but they need to be harmonised and widely adopted to truly reflect what is happening.</description></item><item><title>Distributional impacts of carbon pricing in developing Asia</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/econ_carbonpr/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 11:11:07 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/econ_carbonpr/</guid><description>Distributional impacts of carbon pricing in developing Asia Jan C. Steckel, Ira I. Dorband, Lorenzo Montrone, Hauke Ward, Leonard Missbach, Fabian Hafner, Michael Jakob &amp;amp; Sebastian Renner
Nature Sustainability (2021)
Published: 23 September 2021
Mercator Research Institute on Global Commons and Climate Change, Berlin, Germany
Department Economics of Climate Change, Technische Universität Berlin, Berlin, Germany
https://www.nature.com/articles/s41893-021-00758-8
Abstract Understanding who would be affected in which way by carbon pricing is pivotal for effective and socially equitable policy design, addressing climate change and reducing inequality.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 19: The Central Role of Carbon Prices</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/econ_carbonp/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 10:05:35 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/econ_carbonp/</guid><description>Climate-change policy is a tale of two sciences. The natural sciences have done an admirable job of describing the geophysical aspects of climate change. The science behind global warming is well established. While the timing and regional effects of the changes are not known with certainty, natural scientists have persuasively shown that unchecked CO2 emissions will have dangerous consequences.
But understanding the natural science of climate change is only the first step.</description></item><item><title>Carbon Accounting: 7 representative review papers</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/econ_carbacco/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 21:58:25 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/econ_carbacco/</guid><description>On March 29, 2021, the promulgation of the &amp;ldquo;Guidelines for the Verification of Corporate Greenhouse Gas Emissions Reporting (Trial)&amp;rdquo; means the further improvement of the methodology of China&amp;rsquo;s monitorable-reportable-verifiable (MRV) system.
https://mp.weixin.qq.com/s?__biz=MzU5NDgyNjYxMw==&amp;amp;mid=2247489287&amp;amp;idx=1&amp;amp;sn=19bb0785c3645e9e41b54510ca406754&amp;amp;chksm=fe7a131dc90d9a0b8e59f303a765bc53f72bb48b2c95964191a7a34afec2131be6898a63049f&amp;amp;scene=21#wechat_redirect
2021年3月29日，《企业温室气体排放报告核查指南（试行）》的颁布意味着我国可监测-可报告-可核查（MRV）体系方法学建设的进一步完善。MRV的基础——碳排放数据的准确性、及时性对于碳市场建设至关重要。因此碳核算边界的定义、方法的选取是气候变化相关政策制定的核心要素。然而，无论是碳核算的定义还是方法，时至今日在国内外的研究中都没有形成一致的定义和统一的标准。本文收集了碳核算相关领域最有代表性的7篇文章，分别从定义和方法两个维度对相关研究进行梳理，便于读者对碳核算方法的相关研究建立清晰的逻辑框架。
01 Carbon accounting: a systematic literature review https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0959652612000972
Kristin Stechemesser, Edeltraud Guenther
Technische Universitaet Dresden, Faculty of Economics, Chair of Environmental Management and Accounting, Muenchner Platz 1/3, 01062 Dresden, Germany
Received 27 February 2011, Revised 3 February 2012, Accepted 16 February 2012, Available online 13 March 2012.</description></item><item><title>Carbon Pricing</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/re_0827/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 20:59:40 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/re_0827/</guid><description>Carbon emissions pricing: Some points of reference https://www.europarl.europa.eu/RegData/etudes/BRIE/2020/649352/EPRS_BRI(2020)649352_EN.pdf
Carbon leakage: prevent firms from avoiding emissions rules https://www.europarl.europa.eu/news/en/headlines/society/20210303STO99110/carbon-leakage-prevent-firms-from-avoiding-emissions-rules
CARBON TAX GUIDE:A Handbook for Policy Makers https://documents1.worldbank.org/curated/en/728421535605566659/pdf/129668-V1-WP-PUBLIC-Carbon-Tax-Guide-Main-Report.pdf
United Nations Handbook on carbon taxation for developing countries https://www.un.org/development/desa/financing/sites/www.un.org.development.desa.financing/files/2020-11/Chapter%203_Design_UN%20CarbonTax%20Handbook.pdf
Future-Proof Your Climate Strategy https://hbr.org/2019/05/future-proof-your-climate-strategy
Smart companies are putting their own price on carbon. by Joseph E. Aldy and Gianfranco Gianfrate
From the Harvard Business Review (May–June 2019)
Carbon pricing in the Netherlands (ppt) https://www.pwc.nl/nl/dienstverlening/tax/documents/pwc-state-of-tax-energy-transition-9-2-2021.pdf</description></item><item><title>Concentrated Solar Power (CSP) Vs Photovoltaic (PV): An In-depth Comparison</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/re_0728/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 22:32:42 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/re_0728/</guid><description>The rise in the popularity of solar power energy comes with the expansion of the technologies associated with it. After all, once people realized that the sun can be used to generate electricity, they would understandably find ways on how to do it. And so far, there are two technologies that are used nowadays to generate solar power. These are Concentrated Solar Power (CSP) and Photovoltaic (PV).
But what is the difference between these two?</description></item><item><title>Renewable Energy: Physics, Engineering, Environmental Impacts, Economics and Planning</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/re_0725/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 10:38:36 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/re_0725/</guid><description>Within this economically managed part of the energy sector, renewable energy sources currently provide about 25% of the energy supplied.
A large part of this renewable energy is in the form of biomass energy, either in food crops or in managed forestry providing wood for industrial purposes or for incineration1.
There are two ways to harness solar energy. Passive systems are structures whose design, placement, or materials optimize the use of heat or light directly from the sun.</description></item></channel></rss>