<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>collocations on Blogs of Kai</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/tags/collocations/</link><description>Recent content in collocations on Blogs of Kai</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Jul 2021 15:05:14 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/tags/collocations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Weather</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0717/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jul 2021 15:05:14 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0717/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Wherever you go, no matter what the weather, always bring your own sunshine.&amp;rdquo; Anthony J. D&amp;rsquo;Angelo.
Cards It&amp;rsquo;s great here. Have had unbroken sunshine ever since we arrived. We&amp;rsquo;re having a wonderful time-though in the middle of the day it&amp;rsquo;s just too scorching hot to do anything but lie on the beach soaking up the sunshine. This is the life!
It&amp;rsquo;s been pouring with rain all day. In fact I&amp;rsquo;ve never seen such torrential rain!</description></item><item><title>9 Everyday verbs 3</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0526/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 09:02:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0526/</guid><description>Have Take Break smash verb [transitive] to break something with a lot of force A policeman smashed his camera.
snap verb [transitive] to break something into two pieces, making a loud noise – used especially about long thin objects He snapped the sticks in two.
split verb [transitive] to separate something into two pieces along a straight line Using a sharp knife, split the melon in half.</description></item><item><title>8 Everyday verbs 2</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0524/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 20:24:10 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0524/</guid><description>Get is a very common verb in English, but it is not always appropriate for talking about changes. Note also alternatives to get which can improve your style.
Go, not get People go mad/bald/grey/blind/deaf. Go is often used for sudden, usually negative, changes:
He was very embarrassed and his face went red. Go can also be used for slower colour changes:
The pages of the book had gone yellow over the years.</description></item></channel></rss>