<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Blogs of Kai</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Blogs of Kai</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 16:14:23 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Features of Chinese Food</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_1112/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 16:14:23 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_1112/</guid><description>&lt;p>Chinese food, rich and colorful, has diversified color, aromatic flavor, and excellent taste as its main features. With these three characteristics, it is not only tasty but also a work of art for people to appreciate.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>André Stephan</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_11102/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 22:07:27 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_11102/</guid><description>&lt;p>My research focuses on life cycle environmental assessment and performance in the built environment, from construction materials to cities. I target practical research outcomes that have the potential to inform decision-making in the industry.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>A combined GIS-archetype approach to model residential space heating energy: A case study for the Netherlands including validation</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_1110/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 09:16:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_1110/</guid><description>&lt;p>A transferable residential space heating energy model is developed based on geo-referenced data and archetypes.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Future material demand for automotive lithium-based batteries</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_1108/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 15:49:08 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_1108/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Cappuccino vs. Latte vs. Macchiato - What's the difference?</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_1108/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 09:59:05 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_1108/</guid><description>&lt;p>If you’re exploring the world of milk-based espresso drinks, you may be confused. Almost everyone knows what a Cappuccino is, but what the heck is a Macchiato? and what about a Latte?&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Mung bean cake</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_1107/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 10:30:24 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_1107/</guid><description>&lt;p>Recipe to cook mung bean cake.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>14 Differences Between the Girl you Date and the Woman you Marry</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_1105/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2021 21:48:02 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_1105/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Peer Review File: Global greenhouse gas emissions from residential and commercial building materials and mitigation strategies to 2060</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_11043/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 20:58:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_11043/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Peer Review File: Global greenhouse gas emissions from residential and commercial building materials and mitigation strategies to 2060</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_11044/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 20:58:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_11044/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Building stock energy modeling considering building system composition and long-term change for climate change mitigation of commercial building stocks</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_11042/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 20:48:15 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_11042/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Global construction materials database and stock analysis of residential buildings between 1970-2050</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_1104/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 09:47:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_1104/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Pathways to Net Zero: The Impact of Clean Energy Research</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_1103/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 09:47:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_1103/</guid><description>&lt;p>Explore emerging trends and opportunities to maximize the impact of clean-energy research in &amp;ldquo;Pathways to Net Zero&amp;rdquo; report.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Scientific publishers, scholarly impact and citation analysis</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_1102/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 10:41:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_1102/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Modelling global material stocks and flows for residential and service sector buildings towards 2050</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_1102/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 10:04:18 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_1102/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Energy system decarbonization and productivity gains reduced the coupling of CO2 emissions and economic growth in 73 countries between 1970 and 2016</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_1101/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 21:28:41 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_1101/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Global greenhouse gas emissions from residential and commercial building materials and mitigation strategies to 2060</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_1029/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 11:44:15 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_1029/</guid><description>&lt;p>Implementing several material efficiency strategies together in a High Efficiency (HE) scenario could almost half the baseline emissions. Yet, even in this scenario, the building material sector would require double its current proportional share of emissions to meet a 1.5 °C-compatible target.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>When Should I Use Confidence Intervals, Prediction Intervals, and Tolerance Intervals</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_10265/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 22:54:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_10265/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Four Tips on How to Perform a Regression Analysis that Avoids Common Problems</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_10264/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 22:52:40 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_10264/</guid><description>&lt;p>This blog presents four tips that will help you avoid the more common mistakes of &lt;strong>applied regression analysis&lt;/strong> that I identified in the research literature.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Regression Analysis Tutorial and Examples</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_10263/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 22:48:43 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_10263/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Multiple Regression Analysis: Use Adjusted R-Squared and Predicted R-Squared to Include the Correct Number of Variables</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_10262/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 17:44:19 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_10262/</guid><description>&lt;p>This blog looks at why you should resist the urge to add too many predictors to a regression model, and how the adjusted R-squared and predicted R-squared can help!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>R-squared Shrinkage and Power and Sample Size Guidelines for Regression Analysis</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_1026/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 16:57:20 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_1026/</guid><description>&lt;p>This blog looks at how to obtain an unbiased and reasonably precise estimate of the population R-squared. It also presents power and sample size guidelines for regression analysis.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Maillard Reaction Turns 100</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_1026/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 11:25:40 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_1026/</guid><description>&lt;p>Scientists celebrate the centennial of a reaction that makes cooked food tasty, but also produces worrisome molecules in our meals and bodies.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>What happens when we cook food? Understanding acrylamide formation</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_10262/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 11:25:40 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_10262/</guid><description>&lt;p>The process of heating can also lead to the formation of less favourable substances. One such compound that has received much scientific and media interest over recent years is acrylamide.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>What is the healthiest way to cook vegetables to maximize their nutritional value?</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_1025/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 21:47:53 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_1025/</guid><description>&lt;p>Vegetables lose some nutritional value in transportation, so when possible, buy produce from farmers’ markets.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The memory of expected value and variance</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_1025/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 12:41:56 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_1025/</guid><description>&lt;p>Reviewing the basic statistical concepts: expected value and variance.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Regression analysis: How do I interpret R-squared and assess the Goodness-of-Fit?</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_10242/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 12:05:35 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_10242/</guid><description>&lt;p>Low R-squared values are not always bad and high R-squared values are not always good!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How to Interpret a Regression Model with Low R-squared and Low P values</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_1024/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 10:33:17 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_1024/</guid><description>&lt;p>What if your regression model has significant variables but explains little of the variability? With low P values and a low R-squared.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Integrated assessment modelling (IAM)</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_1021/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 10:37:24 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_1021/</guid><description>&lt;p>A type of scientific modelling that tries to link main features of society and economy with the biosphere and atmosphere into one modelling framework.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Pronunciation of mathematical expressions</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_1019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 10:25:33 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_1019/</guid><description>&lt;p>Common pronunciations (in British English - Gimson,1981) of mathematical and scientific symbols are given in the list below.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>OECD Expert workshop on Economic Modelling of Climate and Related Tipping Points</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_1018/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 19:45:49 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_1018/</guid><description>&lt;p>Emerging evidence highlights the increasing risks of &lt;em>&lt;strong>non-linearities and systemic changes caused by climate change&lt;/strong>&lt;/em>. These include large-scale tipping points in the earth’s climate such as the disintegration of the Greenland and West Antarctic Ice Sheets, permafrost collapse, and the breakdown of the Atlantic Meridional Overturning Circulation among others.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Command Prompt: Basic Commands You Should Know (cmd)</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_1018/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 09:57:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_1018/</guid><description>&lt;p>In Windows, when you open a command prompt, almost always the program that is running is cmd.exe. It&amp;rsquo;s an enhanced NT derivative of the old DOS-based command.com, which is in turn has similarites with the even older CP/M CCP command interpreter.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How effectively delete and add a git submodule</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_1017/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 17:47:11 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_1017/</guid><description>&lt;p>Git Submodules are the concept related to modularity. One git repository can be added to another as a submodule and maintained separately. Instead of being tightly coupled, it is loosely coupled and is easy to maintain.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Complexity Economics</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_1013/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 16:05:34 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_1013/</guid><description>&lt;p>From &lt;strong>The Institute for New Economic Thinking at the Oxford Martin School (INET Oxford)&lt;/strong>&lt;br>
&lt;a href="https://www.inet.ox.ac.uk/research/programmes/complexity-economics/">https://www.inet.ox.ac.uk/research/programmes/complexity-economics/&lt;/a>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>CBAM needs universal adoption of methods for measuring carbon intensity</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_1012/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 10:55:53 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_1012/</guid><description>August 31, 2021 by Dolf Gielen, Massamba Thioye and Francisco Boshell Leave a Comment.
https://energypost.eu/cbam-needs-universal-adoption-of-methods-for-measuring-carbon-intensity/
Europe needs to account for the emissions of imported goods. That cannot happen without the international agreement on standards and certification systems for the carbon intensity of all steps in the value chain for all relevant products. Dolf Gielen and Francisco Boshell at IRENA and Massamba Thioye at the UNFCCC explain that several such systems exist around the world, but they need to be harmonised and widely adopted to truly reflect what is happening.</description></item><item><title>8 Ways To Create Flow According to Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0927/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 10:41:11 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0927/</guid><description>Want to increase your well-being, creativity, and productivity?
If so, you might want to cultivate flow, a concept describing those moments when you’re completely absorbed in a challenging but doable task.
Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi, considered one of the co-founders of positive psychology, was the first to identify and research flow. (If you’re not sure how to pronounce his name, here’s a phonetic guide: “Me high? Cheeks send me high!”)
“The best moments in our lives are not the passive, receptive, relaxing times .</description></item><item><title>How to shoot in Low Light (at night)</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0926/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 10:40:39 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0926/</guid><description>DSLR Tutorial: How to shoot in Low Light (at night) &amp;amp; how to reduce noise!
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AZ9aIB57-Nw
Never go higher than ISO 1600 or the image gets noisy. Keep you shutter speed between1/30s and 1/50s (lights start flickering with higher speed). Aperture should be F/1.2 to F/5.6. Change the contrast of your camera down.</description></item><item><title>Distributional impacts of carbon pricing in developing Asia</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0924/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 11:11:07 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0924/</guid><description>Distributional impacts of carbon pricing in developing Asia Jan C. Steckel, Ira I. Dorband, Lorenzo Montrone, Hauke Ward, Leonard Missbach, Fabian Hafner, Michael Jakob &amp;amp; Sebastian Renner
Nature Sustainability (2021)
Published: 23 September 2021
Mercator Research Institute on Global Commons and Climate Change, Berlin, Germany
Department Economics of Climate Change, Technische Universität Berlin, Berlin, Germany
https://www.nature.com/articles/s41893-021-00758-8
Abstract Understanding who would be affected in which way by carbon pricing is pivotal for effective and socially equitable policy design, addressing climate change and reducing inequality.</description></item><item><title>Guide to OECD’sTrade in Value Added (TiVA)Indicators, 2018 edition</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0917/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 10:05:28 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0917/</guid><description>The Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development (OECD; French: Organisation de Coopération et de Développement Économiques, OCDE) is an intergovernmental economic organisation with 38 member countries.
Generally, OECD members are high-income economies with a very high Human Development Index (HDI) and are regarded as developed countries.
This guide presents the Trade in Value Added (TiVA) indicators published by OECD. The latest indicators were estimated based on the 2018 release of OECD’s annual Inter-Country Input-Output (ICIO) tables which cover the period 2005 to 2015.</description></item><item><title>Webinar: EXIOBASE 3 in SimaPro</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_09152/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 20:38:15 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_09152/</guid><description>On September 18, 2019, the developers of EXIOBASE, 2.-0 LCA Consultants, provided an overview of the database and its applications.
Covering the following topics:
Introduction to Input/Output databases and Hybrid LCAs Overview of EXIOBASE Examples of applications of EXIOBASE using SimaPro</description></item><item><title>Chapter 19: The Central Role of Carbon Prices</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0915/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 10:05:35 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0915/</guid><description>Climate-change policy is a tale of two sciences. The natural sciences have done an admirable job of describing the geophysical aspects of climate change. The science behind global warming is well established. While the timing and regional effects of the changes are not known with certainty, natural scientists have persuasively shown that unchecked CO2 emissions will have dangerous consequences.
But understanding the natural science of climate change is only the first step.</description></item><item><title>Carbon Accounting: 7 representative review papers</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0913/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 21:58:25 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0913/</guid><description>On March 29, 2021, the promulgation of the &amp;ldquo;Guidelines for the Verification of Corporate Greenhouse Gas Emissions Reporting (Trial)&amp;rdquo; means the further improvement of the methodology of China&amp;rsquo;s monitorable-reportable-verifiable (MRV) system.
https://mp.weixin.qq.com/s?__biz=MzU5NDgyNjYxMw==&amp;amp;mid=2247489287&amp;amp;idx=1&amp;amp;sn=19bb0785c3645e9e41b54510ca406754&amp;amp;chksm=fe7a131dc90d9a0b8e59f303a765bc53f72bb48b2c95964191a7a34afec2131be6898a63049f&amp;amp;scene=21#wechat_redirect
2021年3月29日，《企业温室气体排放报告核查指南（试行）》的颁布意味着我国可监测-可报告-可核查（MRV）体系方法学建设的进一步完善。MRV的基础——碳排放数据的准确性、及时性对于碳市场建设至关重要。因此碳核算边界的定义、方法的选取是气候变化相关政策制定的核心要素。然而，无论是碳核算的定义还是方法，时至今日在国内外的研究中都没有形成一致的定义和统一的标准。本文收集了碳核算相关领域最有代表性的7篇文章，分别从定义和方法两个维度对相关研究进行梳理，便于读者对碳核算方法的相关研究建立清晰的逻辑框架。
01 Carbon accounting: a systematic literature review https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0959652612000972
Kristin Stechemesser, Edeltraud Guenther
Technische Universitaet Dresden, Faculty of Economics, Chair of Environmental Management and Accounting, Muenchner Platz 1/3, 01062 Dresden, Germany
Received 27 February 2011, Revised 3 February 2012, Accepted 16 February 2012, Available online 13 March 2012.</description></item><item><title>Beggar Thy Neighbor? On the Competitiveness and Welfare Impacts of the EU’s Proposed Carbon Border Adjustment Mechanism</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0907/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 11:36:29 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0907/</guid><description>Pages Posted: 24 Jul 2021 Last revised: 30 Aug 2021
Jiarui Zhong
Martin-Luther-University Halle-Wittenberg
Jiansuo Pei
Renmin University of China - School of Applied Economics
https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=3891356
Abstract Curbing climate change is gaining increasing consensus globally. While many countries seek to set carbon prices, significant price dispersion and policy stringency continue to raise concerns about competitiveness. To address this issue, the EU has proposed a carbon border adjustment mechanism (CBAM), which aims to level the playing field by levying a carbon price on EU imports.</description></item><item><title>Customizing Figure Layouts Using GridSpec and Other Functions</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0901/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 12:16:46 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0901/</guid><description>https://matplotlib.org/stable/tutorials/intermediate/gridspec.html#sphx-glr-tutorials-intermediate-gridspec-py</description></item><item><title>4 data structures in Python</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0831/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 12:08:51 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0831/</guid><description>Tuple Tuples are used to store multiple items in a single variable.
A tuple is a collection which is ordered and unchangeable.
Tuples are written with round brackets.
thistuple = (&amp;quot;apple&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;banana&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;cherry&amp;quot;) Tuple items are ordered, unchangeable, and allow duplicate values. When we say that tuples are ordered, it means that the items have a defined order, and that order will not change. Tuples are unchangeable, meaning that we cannot change, add or remove items after the tuple has been created.</description></item><item><title>'They would have let Hitler buy ads': Sacha Baron Cohen's scathing attack on Facebook</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0830/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 19:46:17 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0830/</guid><description>Sacha Baron Cohen denounces Facebook, Twitter, YouTube and Google as &amp;lsquo;the greatest propaganda machine in history&amp;rsquo; and culpable for a surge in &amp;lsquo;murderous attacks on religious and ethnic minorities&amp;rsquo;. The actor focuses on Facebook, saying that &amp;lsquo;if you pay them, the platform will run any &amp;ldquo;political&amp;rdquo; ad you want, even if it&amp;rsquo;s a lie&amp;rsquo;. Baron Cohen is speaking on Thursday at Never Is Now, the Anti-Defamation League’s summit on antisemitism and hate in New York, where he is presented with the organisation’s international leadership award.</description></item><item><title>Creating multiple subplots using plt.subplots</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0830/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 11:31:15 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0830/</guid><description>pyplot.subplots creates a figure and a grid of subplots with a single call, while providing reasonable control over how the individual plots are created. For more advanced use cases you can use GridSpec for a more general subplot layout or Figure.add_subplot for adding subplots at arbitrary locations within the figure.
https://matplotlib.org/stable/gallery/subplots_axes_and_figures/subplots_demo.html
matplotlib.pyplot.subplots
matplotlib.pyplot.subplots(nrows=1, ncols=1, *, sharex=False, sharey=False, squeeze=True, subplot_kw=None, gridspec_kw=None, **fig_kw)
Returns:
fig: The matplotlib.pyplot.figure object to be used as a container for all the subplots.</description></item><item><title>Carbon Pricing</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0827/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 20:59:40 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0827/</guid><description>Carbon emissions pricing: Some points of reference https://www.europarl.europa.eu/RegData/etudes/BRIE/2020/649352/EPRS_BRI(2020)649352_EN.pdf
Carbon leakage: prevent firms from avoiding emissions rules https://www.europarl.europa.eu/news/en/headlines/society/20210303STO99110/carbon-leakage-prevent-firms-from-avoiding-emissions-rules
CARBON TAX GUIDE:A Handbook for Policy Makers https://documents1.worldbank.org/curated/en/728421535605566659/pdf/129668-V1-WP-PUBLIC-Carbon-Tax-Guide-Main-Report.pdf
United Nations Handbook on carbon taxation for developing countries https://www.un.org/development/desa/financing/sites/www.un.org.development.desa.financing/files/2020-11/Chapter%203_Design_UN%20CarbonTax%20Handbook.pdf
Future-Proof Your Climate Strategy https://hbr.org/2019/05/future-proof-your-climate-strategy
Smart companies are putting their own price on carbon. by Joseph E. Aldy and Gianfranco Gianfrate
From the Harvard Business Review (May–June 2019)
Carbon pricing in the Netherlands (ppt) https://www.pwc.nl/nl/dienstverlening/tax/documents/pwc-state-of-tax-energy-transition-9-2-2021.pdf</description></item><item><title>The Shortest History of Europe</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0827/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 19:09:58 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0827/</guid><description>CHAPTER 1. Europe Classical and Medieval1 EUROPEAN CIVILISATION IS UNIQUE because it is the only civilisation which has imposed itself on the rest of the world. It did this by conquest and settlement; by its economic power; by the power of its ideas; and because it had things that everyone else wanted. Today every country on earth uses the discoveries of science and the technologies that flow from it, and science was a European invention.</description></item><item><title>On the competitiveness impact of the EU CBAM: An Input-Output approach</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0826/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 10:52:33 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0826/</guid><description>Abstract While many countries seek to set a price for carbon emissions,
significant price dispersion and relative stringency keep raising concerns on carbon leakage.
We quantify the competitiveness impact of the EU CBAM based on the multi-regional Input-Output approach.</description></item><item><title>Emerging role of Geographical Information System (GIS), Life Cycle Assessment (LCA) and spatial LCA (GIS-LCA) in sustainable bioenergy planning</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0822/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2021 22:00:18 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0822/</guid><description>https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0960852417303516#f0010
Abstract Sustainability of a bioenergy project depends on precise assessment of biomass resource, planning of cost-effective logistics and evaluation of possible environmental implications. In this context, this paper reviews the role and applications of geo-spatial tool such as Geographical Information System (GIS) for precise agro-residue resource assessment, biomass logistic and power plant design. Further, application of Life Cycle Assessment (LCA) in understanding the potential impact of agro-residue bioenergy generation on different ecosystem services has also been reviewed and limitations associated with LCA variability and uncertainty were discussed.</description></item><item><title>On the competitiveness impact of the EU CBAM: An Input-Output approach</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0821/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Aug 2021 16:37:59 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0821/</guid><description>Jiarui ZHONG, Martin-Luther-University, Halle-Wittenberg, Germany.
Email: Jiarui.zhong@wiwi.uni-halle.de
Jiansuo PEI (corresponding author), School of Applied Economics,
Renmin University of China, 59 Zhongguancun Street, Beijing 100872,
China, Email: jspei@ruc.edu.cn; Tel: +86-10-82500208</description></item><item><title>LC-IMPACT: A regionalized life cycle damage assessment method</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0818/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 12:19:10 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0818/</guid><description>https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1111/jiec.13018
Abstract Here, we present the LC-IMPACT method that provides characterization factors at the damage level for 11 impact categories related to three areas of protection (human health, ecosystem quality, natural resources).</description></item><item><title>Nature-based-solutions--Scenarios for the Global Land Outlook 2</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0817/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 09:25:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0817/</guid><description>This study quantifies the potential effects of land restoration for soil, food, water, biodiversity and climate change at the global and regional levels, using three global land-use scenarios up to 2050.
https://www.pbl.nl/en/publications/the-global-potential-for-land-restoration-scenarios-for-the-global-land-outlook-2
https://www.pbl.nl/sites/default/files/downloads/pbl-2021-the-global-potential-for-land-restoration-glo2-3898.pdf
https://themasites.pbl.nl/nature-based-solutions/nature-based-solutions
Nature-based solutions and scenarios Nature-based Solutions (BbS) are actions that enable the protection, sustainable management and restoration of natural and managed ecosystems, that can simultaneously provide human well-being an biodiversity benefits.
Nature-based solutions (NbS) include restoration, management, and rehabilitation measures, as well as conservation of ecosystems, that enhance nature’s contribution to people, such as agroforestry, conservation agriculture, assisted natural regeneration and urban green and blue spaces.</description></item><item><title>Advanced Course on LCA —— Session 3: Economic Allocation</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0816/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 16:13:31 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0816/</guid><description>Session 3 Purpose This software session focuses on reproducing the results of an LCA paper on economic allocation, defining functional flows and identifying multi functional processes, with the software program CMLCA. In today’s exercises, you will learn:
to understand the main principles of economic allocation; how such analyses work in CMLCA software. You may perform the exercise alone or together with (a) colleague(s) in a virtual room, and again, you don’t have to hand in the results.</description></item><item><title>Dutch Golden Age: Crash Course European History</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0815/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 21:29:57 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0815/</guid><description>The Dutch Golden Age was a period in the history of the Netherlands, roughly spanning the era from 1588 (the birth of the Dutch Republic) to 1672 (the Rampjaar, &amp;ldquo;Disaster Year&amp;rdquo;), in which Dutch trade, science, and art and the Dutch military were among the most acclaimed in the world. The first section is characterized by the Eighty Years' War, which ended in 1648. The Golden Age continued in peacetime during the Dutch Republic until the end of the century, when costly conflicts, including the Franco-Dutch War and War of the Spanish Succession fuelled economic decline.</description></item><item><title>Economic Allocation: Examples and Derived Decision Tree</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0815/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 09:24:52 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0815/</guid><description>https://link.springer.com/content/pdf/10.1007/BF02978533.pdf
Economic Allocation: Examples and Derived Decision Tree Jeroen B. Guinde*, Reinout Heijungs and Gjah Huppes
Institute of Environmental Sciences (CML), Leiden University, P.O. Box 9518, 2300 RA Leiden, The Netherlands
Int J LCA 9 (1) 23 - 33 (2004)
Abstract Goal, Scope and Background. In the recently published (Dutch) Handbook on LCA, economic allocation is advised as baseline method for most allocation situations in a detailed LCA. Although the Handbook on LCA aimed to provide a &amp;lsquo;cookbook&amp;rsquo; with operational guidelines for conducting each step of an LCA, this was not completely achieved for the allocation step.</description></item><item><title>Proper or messy allocation?--Systematic approach to identifying and solving multi-functionality in LCA</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0814/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2021 11:20:07 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0814/</guid><description>Avoided burden1
Most existing LCA databases today do not include multi-functional processes.
including ecoinvent MF is &amp;lsquo;solved&amp;rsquo; by database developers by delivering only mono-functional datasets.
Mostly, practitioners cannot change this methodological decision anymore and often don&amp;rsquo;t realize that they are handling (&amp;lsquo;accepting&amp;rsquo;) more MF issues than they realize.
Consequently, most software doesn&amp;rsquo;t include ways to address MF.
While it is known as one of the most determining factors of LCA results.</description></item><item><title>Land use indicators in LCA</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0810/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 09:54:21 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0810/</guid><description>Principles for life cycle inventories of land use on a global scale Thomas Koellner, Laura de Baan, Tabea Beck, Miguel Brandão, Barbara Civit, Mark Goedkoop, Manuele Margni, Llorenç Milà i Canals, Ruedi Müller-Wenk, Bo Weidema &amp;amp; Bastian Wittstock
The International Journal of Life Cycle Assessment volume 18, pages1203–1215 (2013)
https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s11367-012-0392-0
Land use elementary flows In LCA, land occupation and land transformation can be distinguished as basic types of land use elementary flows (Milà i Canals et al.</description></item><item><title>Literature review on the land use of future energy</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0809/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 11:26:59 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0809/</guid><description>https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S1364032108001354
Land use and electricity generation: A life-cycle analysis Renewable and Sustainable Energy Reviews
Volume 13, Issues 6–7, August–September 2009, Pages 1465-1474
Vasilis Fthenakis¹, Hyung Chul Kim²
¹ National Photovoltaic Environmental Research Center, Brookhaven National Laboratory, Bldg 475B, Upton, NY 11973, United States
² Center for Life Cycle Analysis, Columbia University, New York, NY 10027, United States
Abstract Renewable-energy sources often are regarded as dispersed and difficult to collect, thus requiring substantial land resources in comparison to conventional energy sources.</description></item><item><title>Waste is not a service</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0808/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2021 11:03:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0808/</guid><description>https://link.springer.com/content/pdf/10.1007/s11367-021-01955-5.pdf
Almost every overview of LCA gives a graphical indication of the idea of a life cycle. Such diagrams consist of a linear sequence or network of blocks, connected with arrows, representing the major life stages of a product life cycle. Examples from recent textbooks on LCA can be found in Klöpffer and Grahl (2014, p. 2), Jolliet et al. (2016, p. 36), and Hauschild et al. (2018, p. 120). All such flow diagrams agree on the basic setup of a chronological order: resource becomes products, products are used, and it all ends with disposal of waste.</description></item><item><title>Concentrated Solar Power (CSP) Vs Photovoltaic (PV): An In-depth Comparison</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0728/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 22:32:42 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0728/</guid><description>The rise in the popularity of solar power energy comes with the expansion of the technologies associated with it. After all, once people realized that the sun can be used to generate electricity, they would understandably find ways on how to do it. And so far, there are two technologies that are used nowadays to generate solar power. These are Concentrated Solar Power (CSP) and Photovoltaic (PV).
But what is the difference between these two?</description></item><item><title>Love handles: What causes them, and how do you get rid of them?</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0725/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 14:42:10 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0725/</guid><description>https://www.healthline.com/health/what-causes-love-handles
What are love handles? &amp;ldquo;Love handles&amp;rdquo; are areas of skin that extend outward from the hips. When combined with tight clothing, love handles become more pronounced, but they aren&amp;rsquo;t caused by tight clothing alone. They indicate excess fat accumulation around the hips and abdominal area.
What causes love handles?
The underlying cause of love handles is fat retention.
Generally speaking, fat cells accumulate when your body takes in too many calories or you don&amp;rsquo;t burn as many calories as you&amp;rsquo;re consuming.</description></item><item><title>Renewable Energy: Physics, Engineering, Environmental Impacts, Economics and Planning</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0725/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 10:38:36 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0725/</guid><description>Within this economically managed part of the energy sector, renewable energy sources currently provide about 25% of the energy supplied.
A large part of this renewable energy is in the form of biomass energy, either in food crops or in managed forestry providing wood for industrial purposes or for incineration1.
There are two ways to harness solar energy. Passive systems are structures whose design, placement, or materials optimize the use of heat or light directly from the sun.</description></item><item><title>30 Tough but Very Important Advanced Verbs for Daily Use</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0721/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2021 20:09:18 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0721/</guid><description>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WGce2fBK0aM&amp;amp;t=768s
to accomplish
to succeed in doing something, especially after trying very hard
= achieve
Mission accomplished.
Try to accomplish your aim with diligence.
to accumulate
to gradually get more and more money, possessions, knowledge etc over a period of time
eg. Capitalism is not just about accumulation.
In everyday English, people usually say build up rather than accumulate.
to be beware
used to warn someone to be careful because something is dangerous</description></item><item><title>Global Sustainability Accounting—Developing EXIOBASE for Multi-Regional Footprint Analysis</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0719/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 09:57:38 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0719/</guid><description>A global multi-regional input−output database (EXIOBASE) with a focus on environmentally relevant activities, allowing insights into the production-related impacts and consumption footprints1.
1. Introduction 1.1. Developments in Multi-Regional Input-Output Analysis (MRIO) Harmonization Compared to other databases, EXIOBASE has a clear environmental and resource focus with high levels of detail in primary production.
Harmonizing and detailing supply and use tables (SUT):
Gathering SUT from the relevant statistical offices. In the specific case of EXIOBASE, data is gathered from the EU27 via Eurostat, and other SUT and IO tables from 16 other countries.</description></item><item><title>Of Studies</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0718/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2021 12:15:36 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0718/</guid><description>Of Studies by Francis Bacon (1625)
Studies serve for delight, for ornament1, and for ability. Their chief use for delight is in privateness and retiring; for ornament, is in discourse; and for ability, is in the judgment and disposition of business. For expert men can execute, and perhaps judge of particulars2, one by one; but the general counseles, and the plots and marshalling of affairs, come best from those that learned.</description></item><item><title>Weather</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0717/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jul 2021 15:05:14 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0717/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Wherever you go, no matter what the weather, always bring your own sunshine.&amp;rdquo; Anthony J. D&amp;rsquo;Angelo.
Cards It&amp;rsquo;s great here. Have had unbroken sunshine ever since we arrived. We&amp;rsquo;re having a wonderful time-though in the middle of the day it&amp;rsquo;s just too scorching hot to do anything but lie on the beach soaking up the sunshine. This is the life!
It&amp;rsquo;s been pouring with rain all day. In fact I&amp;rsquo;ve never seen such torrential rain!</description></item><item><title>Special issue of Euro 2020: England vs Italy</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0712/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 09:24:55 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0712/</guid><description>Live blogs From MARCE and EURO 2020 offical.
Minute 1: Kick off in the Euro 2020 final!
Here we go then! In the rainy conditions, Italy vs England kicks off. It&amp;rsquo;s the Euro 2020 final. Let&amp;rsquo;s see who replaces Portugal to become the champions of Europe.
Minute 2: England go ahead already!
England take a very early lead in this Euro 2020 final, launching a counter attack from an Italian corner.</description></item><item><title>7 Things Tolkien Said About Life 7 Things Tolkien Said About Life — 7 Comments</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0710/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 22:42:15 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0710/</guid><description>J.R.R. Tolkien wrote many books, including the Middle-earth stories. He is particularly known for The Lord of the Rings and like many stories of an epic journey, LOTR lets us take away lessons we can apply to our life.
No matter how surreal his epic stories are, the pieces of wisdom reflected in them mirror that of the wisdom we must gain to champion our life here on earth.
7 Things Tolkien Said About Life</description></item><item><title>From Satellite to Supply Chain: New Approaches Connect Earth Observation to Economic Decisions</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0710/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 10:10:29 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0710/</guid><description>why we need more transparent supply chains? A growing share of countries’ environmental and social impacts occurs abroad; Businesses and shareholders need to identify and evaluate the potential
environmental impacts and biodiversity loss of their foreign producers; Individual consumers increasingly ask for the locations and magnitude of the impacts associated with their choices; Contributing to an accountability framework that would trigger higher environmental standards in the specific industry of producing countries.</description></item><item><title>Spatially-explicit footprints of agricultural commodities Mapping carbon emissions embodied in Brazil's soy exports</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0706/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 17:08:59 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0706/</guid><description>Abstract LCA faces limitations when it comes to addressing spatial and temporal variability in production, transportation and manufacturing systems. By the integration of LCA principles with enhanced physical trade flow analysis. Estimating the carbon footprint1 of Brazilian soy exports over the period 2010–2015 based on over 90000 individual traded flows of beans, oil and protein cake from the municipality of origin through international markets. A large spatial variability in co2 across sourcing areas, importers and sub-stages has been detected.</description></item><item><title>Have/Get/Make/Let—Learn when to use causative verbs.</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0703/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 09:52:27 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0703/</guid><description>LET = Permit Something To Happen I don’t let my kids watch violent movies.
Mary’s father won’t let her adopt a puppy because he’s allergic to dogs.
Our boss doesn’t let us eat lunch at our desks; we have to eat in the cafeteria.
Oops! I wasn’t paying attention while cooking, and I let the food burn.
Don’t let the advertising expenses surpass $1000.
MAKE = Force Or Require Someone To Take An Action My ex-boyfriend loved sci-fi and made me watch every episode of his favorite show.</description></item><item><title>Mapping global patterns of land use decision-making</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0630/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 11:01:39 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0630/</guid><description>ŽigaMalekaPeter H.Verburgab
Department of Environmental Geography, Institute for Environmental Studies (IVM), Vrije Universiteit Amsterdam, De Boelelaan 1087, 1081 HV Amsterdam, The Netherlands
Available online 23 September 2020.
How such local-scale patterns of decision-making can be used to explain land-use change globally is unknown. Using a collection of local studies from a literature review, we studied the contextual conditions of different modes of land-use change decision-making and present global maps of the potential distribution of decision-making in land-use change.</description></item><item><title>Is beer better (or worse) for you than wine?</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0627/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 23:34:41 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0627/</guid><description>Few drinks (save tea or coffee) divide the world so spectacularly as beer or wine. There’s no accounting for taste, of course – but there are subtle differences in the way they affect your body and determine your health. Is one more fattening than another? How do their heart benefits compare? And which gives the worse hangover?
BBC Future has combed through the data to bust some of the myths surrounding two of the world’s favourite drinks.</description></item><item><title>What you should know about beer?</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0626/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 21:50:46 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0626/</guid><description>BEER: WHERE DO ALL THOSE FLAVOURS COME FROM? There are thousands of different ways that yeast, malt, and hops that can be combined to make beer, and all those combinations can lead to lots of interesting outcomes. There are also a LOT of additives you can put in beer to give it different flavours, but I’m going to focus on the core ingredients: yeast, hops, and malt.
Yeast Yeast is a fungus.</description></item><item><title>How do I set nudge distance in Illustrator?</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0623/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 18:33:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0623/</guid><description>You can change your nudge increments distance in the Preferences Panel(Keyboard increments).
Setting nudge distance/keyboard increment Uncheck snap to pixel in the view tab Change the keyboard increment in the Edit tab -&amp;gt;preference from 1 pixel(by fault) to a tiny one which you want. Tip also: the super nudge is a 10-times shift by holding the shift when using the arrow key.</description></item><item><title>MSc Industrial Ecology programme</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0618/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 10:37:22 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0618/</guid><description>Industrial Ecology The MSc Industrial Ecology (joint degree Leiden University and TU Delft) is an interdisciplinary and international programme, which focuses on the analysis of sustainability problems and the design and implementation of solutions for these problems; all from a socio-technical system perspective. The aim of the programme is to educate students to become researchers or practitioners who can contribute to the development of solutions for persistent sustainability problems, such as related to resource depletion and climate change.</description></item><item><title>Why Was My Paper Rejected without Review?</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0617/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 09:54:35 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0617/</guid><description>A guidance highlighting why your paper was rejected by Environmental Science &amp;amp; Technology and what basic characteristics your paper should possess so it can move forward.
(For the original: https://pubs.acs.org/doi/10.1021/acs.est.0c05784)
Highlights:</description></item><item><title>Moving the cursor point in word</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0614/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 17:59:34 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0614/</guid><description>The text you type appears wherever the insertion/cursor point is positioned in the current document. Moving the insertion point around the screen is a critical part of creating and editing documents. To move the insertion point around the screen, you can use either the keyboard or the mouse. Table 1-1 lists ways to move the insertion point by using keystrokes.
https://www.trainingconnection.com/word/lessons/moving-cursor.php
Keystroke Result Up, Down, Left, or Right Arrow Moves the insertion point to the previous or next line or character.</description></item><item><title>How to edit/modify/customise Endnote references styles?</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0613/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 10:28:21 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0613/</guid><description>You will only be able to edit the style if the style is saved to your computer.
Go to Tools - Output styles - select the style to edit. Select Citations to view how the intext citation displays and make any changes. Select Bibliography - Templates to view the templates for the different reference types and make changes. Most of changes would be made in these places.
When you close the style window, you will be prompted to save changes you have made.</description></item><item><title>Alternative words and humour</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0612/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 22:25:16 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0612/</guid><description>Some alternatives for please, sorry, fine, sad, tired and bored.
Alternatives for please Would you mind&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;d appreciate it if you could&amp;hellip; Would you be able to &amp;hellip; I wonder if you might&amp;hellip; Alernatives for sorry It was thoughtless of me&amp;hellip; It was careless of me&amp;hellip; I owe you a pology for my awful behaviour. I take full responsibility for my actions. I sincerely apologise. For I&amp;rsquo;m fine (I) couldn&amp;rsquo;t be better!</description></item><item><title>First run with Garmin forerunner 245</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0609/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 18:13:24 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0609/</guid><description>Not to be so professional and just for the recording of every running exercise in Leiden I chose the plain and runner-designed Garmin forerunner 245.
Plenty of choice at Garmin Garmin is working hard in the field of wearables. In recent years, the American company has successfully shifted its focus from navigation boxes for the car to GPS-based sports watches and bicycle computers. In the first quarter of this year, Garmin was number three worldwide in terms of numbers of smartwatches sold, with only Samsung and Apple to tolerate.</description></item><item><title>Manual of EXIOBASE V3.8 updates</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0609/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 09:33:47 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0609/</guid><description>v3.8 was released in November 2020, provided with a full re-estimate of the time-series (to 2021) that heavily relies on &amp;ldquo;now-casting&amp;rdquo; economic structure (and environmental extensions).
The time-series extends into the future (2021), but this is based on the now-casting procedure and projections of GDP and aggregate trade of the IMF.
Main updates Macroeconomic and trade data for recent years
Updated to 2018 macroeconomic data from UN, and GDP &amp;amp; gross import/export projections until 2022 from IMF.</description></item><item><title>Feel struggling to response 'How are you'</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0607/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 20:40:07 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0607/</guid><description>Since I&amp;rsquo;m here I couldn&amp;rsquo;t count that how many times people asking me &amp;lsquo;how are you&amp;rsquo; and I actually don&amp;rsquo;t know how to response this due to the difference of the greeting ways.
Today I came across Grace in the corridor of our apartment building. Again I was asking &amp;lsquo;How are you?&amp;rsquo; It could be simple as a normal greeting way here but I just not be adapted to it. At the hometown we just say people&amp;rsquo;s name if he/she is an acquaintance.</description></item><item><title>GIA in the EIOA class: exploring the impact of Brexit (2)</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_06072/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 15:35:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_06072/</guid><description>The Brexit topic from the BBC News.
(The Brexit topic link/Group drive)
Scenario analysis source: Assessing energy and economic impacts of large-scale policy shocks based on Input-Output analysis: Application to Brexit
Research background from the latest Brexit News Farmers should not fear Australia trade deal, UK minister says 27/05/2021
Keywords: free trade deal with Au; competition of UK farmers; gateway to TPP.
Farmers have warned they could struggle to compete if Australia was given tariff-free access to UK markets.</description></item><item><title>GIA in the EIOA class: exploring the impact of Brexit (1)</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0607/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 15:34:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0607/</guid><description>UK companies can and should see the current high-uncertainty environment as a spur to rethink their supply chain strategies and make them more resilient.
https://www.mckinsey.com/featured-insights/europe/brexit-the-bigger-picture-rethinking-supply-chains-in-a-time-of-uncertainty
Why Europe is so critical in British supply chains The EU is the UK&amp;rsquo;s largest trading partner, accounting for approximately half of both imports and exports of goods (Exhibit1). Moreover, a large proportion of the UK’s imports from and exports to the EU are in the form of intermediary products—an indicator of the high degree of interconnectedness between UK and EU supply chains (Exhibit 2).</description></item><item><title>Linking Global Crop and Livestock Consumption to Local Production Hotspots</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0606/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 09:42:03 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0606/</guid><description>Identifying production hotspots for global crop and livestock consumption by a Spatially Explicit Multi-Reginal Input-Output model ( Zhongxiao&amp;rsquo;s work on Global Food Security).
Keywords: primary crops; animal husbandry; spatially explicit; Multi-Regional Input-Output(MRIO) analysis.
Research background Food security is challenged by increasing global food demand driven by population growth and animal-based diets. More crop production requires increasing areas of land and fresh water, causing associated environmental impacts1. Also livestock should be a focus as their feed contains harmful ingredients2 which will released to our environment finally.</description></item><item><title>All about the lettuce</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0602/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 18:46:44 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0602/</guid><description>&amp;lsquo;Leaf lettuce, head lettuce, green lettuce, red lettuce….who knew there were so many kinds of lettuce? This is your handy guide to knowing what kind of lettuce your are eating with.&amp;rsquo;
Types of Lettuce Iceberg Butterhead Romaine Leaf Kale ICEBERG LETTUCE This is probably the most famous and recognizable form of head lettuce. Iceberg lettuce is also sometimes referred to as crisphead, and it is a pale green leafy vegetable that forms into a tight cabbage style head.</description></item><item><title>Assessing the spatially explicit global footprints of European net-zero strategies</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0602/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 10:11:09 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0602/</guid><description>“Someone’s sitting in the shade today because someone planted a tree a long time ago” &amp;mdash;Warren Buffett.
Research aim Building a detailed, spatially explicit, internationally trade linked GMRIO of food and energy systems at a ~5arc min(9km) resolution. Exploring current environmental and social footprints of these systems and the threats or opportunities presented by EU net-zero strategies. Incorporating net-zero pathways from the literature into the model from both production and consumption perspectives, and connecting land suitability maps for future renewable energy, mining, and agriculture potentials.</description></item><item><title>Impacts of COVID-19 and fiscal stimuli on global emissions and the Paris Agreement</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0528/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 11:06:53 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0528/</guid><description>Published:22 December 2020
Authors: Yuli Shan, Jiamin Ou, Daoping Wang, Zhao Zeng, Shaohui Zhang, Dabo Guan &amp;amp; Klaus Hubacek
https://www.nature.com/articles/s41558-020-00977-5
Scenarios of global lockdown and effects on CO2 emissions Economic impacts model ARIO model：Adaptive Regional Input-Output Model can be used to analyse the disaster-induced influence on regional economy.
The Leontief production function does not allow for substitution between inputs.
Scenarios of lockdown Lockdown periods Strictness of the first lockdown period Strictness of future lockdown periods Labour loss dominates the economic loss in the model.</description></item><item><title>RP Project</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0526/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 10:10:16 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0526/</guid><description>Measuring in Arc-Seconds The source link
USGS: United States Geological Survey. DEM: Digital elevation model [Wiki search](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Digital_elevation_model#:~:text=A%20digital%20elevation%20model%20(DEM,to%20a%20discrete%20global%20grid) Some USGS DEM data is stored in a format that utilizes three, five, or 30 arc-seconds of longitude and latitude to register cell values. The geographic reference system treats the globe as if it were a sphere divided into 360 equal parts called degrees.
Said differently, an arc-second represents the distance of latitude or longitude across the earth&amp;rsquo;s surface with the angle of one second.</description></item><item><title>9 Everyday verbs 3</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0526/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 09:02:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0526/</guid><description>Have Take Break smash verb [transitive] to break something with a lot of force
A policeman smashed his camera.
snap verb [transitive] to break something into two pieces, making a loud noise – used especially about long thin objects
He snapped the sticks in two.
split verb [transitive] to separate something into two pieces along a straight line
Using a sharp knife, split the melon in half.</description></item><item><title>PhD transferable skills</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0525/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 09:09:10 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0525/</guid><description>Here are examples of PhD skill sets and ways to describe them by University of Michigan.
Sometimes it&amp;rsquo;s difficult for PhD students to identify what skills they have since the academic experience is not necessarily focused on articulating skill sets. We also often find that PhD students struggle, understandably, to present the transferability of their academic experiences to non-academic contexts. Here are examples of PhD skill sets and ways to describe them.</description></item><item><title>8 Everyday verbs 2</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0524/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 20:24:10 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0524/</guid><description>Get is a very common verb in English, but it is not always appropriate for talking about changes. Note
also alternatives to get which can improve your style.
Go, not get People go mad/bald/grey/blind/deaf. Go is often used for sudden, usually negative, changes:
He was very embarrassed and his face went red. Go can also be used for slower colour changes:
The pages of the book had gone yellow over the years.</description></item><item><title>Writing your dissertation - working with your supervisor</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0523/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 11:46:04 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0523/</guid><description>Source
Your supervisor Before you begin your dissertation, it is highly likely you will be assigned a supervisor to oversee your progress from first steps to completion. Your supervisor will help you formulate ideas and give you guidance on how best to develop your research topic and course of action. But you need to always remember that this is your project, and your supervisor will not provide you with content or additional lessons on a particular topic.</description></item><item><title>Global Scenarios of Resource and Emissions Savings from systemic Material Efficiency in Buildings and Cars</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0521/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 11:12:40 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0521/</guid><description>Abstract Here we present a high-resolution approach for tracking material flows and energy use of products throughout their life cycles, focusing on passenger vehicles and residential buildings. We estimate future changes in material flows and operational energy use due to increased yields, light-weight designs, material substitution, increased service efficiency, extended service life, and increased reuse and recycling.
Main Text comprised of 20 countries/regions six major climate-relevant materials (aluminium, cement, copper, plastics, steel, wood) for the period 2016 - 2060.</description></item><item><title>Covid 19 Self Testing</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0518/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 22:07:22 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0518/</guid><description>Interesting warnings These kits are only designed for human use．
Use a separate test kit for each person. You can only use each item in　the test kit once. Do not re-use the items．
Do not eat or drink for at least 30 minutes before doing the test to
reduce the risk of spoiling the test.
What you need to do Prepare your test area and check your test kit contents Set up your test Take your swab sample Process the swab sample Read your result Report your result Safely dispose of your test kit Store the test kit at room temperature or in a cool dry place (2°C</description></item><item><title>About me</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/about/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/about/</guid><description>I received my PhD scholarship from China in July 2020 when the covid epidemic is spreading around the world. After a long holiday for me, I began my work in industrial ecology at Leiden University in February 2021.
My family
Seriously I am not a foodie(eat simple while working) but I Do like food and cooking. In my spare time (really scarce), I will dive into my kitchen and make pasta.</description></item><item><title>Changing Fonts in hugo website</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_05172/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_05172/</guid><description>&lt;p>Thanks to Damien. I got new hugo shortcodes for the fonts update in this website.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>EIOA Class: Integrated Group Assignment(IGA)</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_05173/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_05173/</guid><description>&lt;p>Each group is expected to perform a research question about two real-world issues: BREXIT and national stimulus plans.&lt;br>
in a post COVID-19 world.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Make Your Website Social Media Card</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0517/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0517/</guid><description>Make Your Website Social Media Card-able on Twitter, Facebook and More See the original link
We all want our websites to be shared on Twitter, Facebook and all the different channels of social media. Whether they are our own websites that have our blogs and profiles or websites we built for other people. We all value those valuable clicks, so as a means of seduction to make our links clickable, we need to make them look attractive and pretty.</description></item><item><title>Tackling Climate Change with Machine Learning</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0517/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0517/</guid><description>Identify climate change problems where existing gaps can be filled by machine learning.
https://arxiv.org/pdf/1906.05433v2.pdf
Highlights Industry ML demonstrates considerable potential for reducing industrial GHG emissions under the following circumstances.
when there is enough accessible, high-quality data around specific processes or transport routes. when firms have an incentive to share their proprietary data and/or algorithms with researchers and other firms. When aspects of production or shipping can be readily fine-tuned or adjusted, and there are clear objective functions.</description></item><item><title>Hugo Figure Shortcode</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_05162/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_05162/</guid><description>Hugo has figure shortcode built-in, so you can easily add figure captions or hyperlink rel attributes to images. Documentations can be found here:
https://gohugo.io/content-management/shortcodes/#figure
This theme has 3 CSS classes made for figure elements:
big: images will break the width limit of main content area. left: images will float to the left. right: images will float to the right. If a figure has no class set, the image will behave just like a normal markdown image: !</description></item><item><title>Rich Content -- Bult-in Shortcode</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0516/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0516/</guid><description>&lt;p>Hugo ships with several &lt;a href="https://gohugo.io/content-management/shortcodes/#use-hugos-built-in-shortcodes">Built-in Shortcodes&lt;/a> for rich content, along with a &lt;a href="https://gohugo.io/about/hugo-and-gdpr/">Privacy Config&lt;/a> and a set of Simple Shortcodes that enable static and no-JS versions of various social media embeds.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0515/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0515/</guid><description>&lt;p>This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Math Typesetting</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0328/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0328/</guid><description>&lt;p>Mathematical notation in a Hugo project can be enabled by using third party JavaScript libraries.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>