<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Paul Behrens on Blogs of Kai</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/tags/paul-behrens/</link><description>Recent content in Paul Behrens on Blogs of Kai</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 10:38:36 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/tags/paul-behrens/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Renewable Energy: Physics, Engineering, Environmental Impacts, Economics and Planning</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0725/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 10:38:36 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0725/</guid><description>Within this economically managed part of the energy sector, renewable energy sources currently provide about 25% of the energy supplied.
A large part of this renewable energy is in the form of biomass energy, either in food crops or in managed forestry providing wood for industrial purposes or for incineration1.
There are two ways to harness solar energy. Passive systems are structures whose design, placement, or materials optimize the use of heat or light directly from the sun.</description></item><item><title>Assessing the spatially explicit global footprints of European net-zero strategies</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0602/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 10:11:09 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0602/</guid><description>“Someone’s sitting in the shade today because someone planted a tree a long time ago” &amp;mdash;Warren Buffett.
Research aim Building a detailed, spatially explicit, internationally trade linked GMRIO of food and energy systems at a ~5arc min(9km) resolution. Exploring current environmental and social footprints of these systems and the threats or opportunities presented by EU net-zero strategies. Incorporating net-zero pathways from the literature into the model from both production and consumption perspectives, and connecting land suitability maps for future renewable energy, mining, and agriculture potentials.</description></item><item><title>RP Project</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0526/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 10:10:16 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0526/</guid><description>Measuring in Arc-Seconds The source link
USGS: United States Geological Survey. DEM: Digital elevation model [Wiki search](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Digital_elevation_model#:~:text=A%20digital%20elevation%20model%20(DEM,to%20a%20discrete%20global%20grid) Some USGS DEM data is stored in a format that utilizes three, five, or 30 arc-seconds of longitude and latitude to register cell values. The geographic reference system treats the globe as if it were a sphere divided into 360 equal parts called degrees. Said differently, an arc-second represents the distance of latitude or longitude across the earth&amp;rsquo;s surface with the angle of one second.</description></item></channel></rss>