<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Environmentally Extended Input–Output Analysis on Blogs of Kai</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/categories/environmentally-extended-inputoutput-analysis/</link><description>Recent content in Environmentally Extended Input–Output Analysis on Blogs of Kai</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 09:57:38 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/categories/environmentally-extended-inputoutput-analysis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Global Sustainability Accounting—Developing EXIOBASE for Multi-Regional Footprint Analysis</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0719/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 09:57:38 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0719/</guid><description>A global multi-regional input−output database (EXIOBASE) with a focus on environmentally relevant activities, allowing insights into the production-related impacts and consumption footprints1.
1. Introduction 1.1. Developments in Multi-Regional Input-Output Analysis (MRIO) Harmonization Compared to other databases, EXIOBASE has a clear environmental and resource focus with high levels of detail in primary production.
Harmonizing and detailing supply and use tables (SUT):
Gathering SUT from the relevant statistical offices. In the specific case of EXIOBASE, data is gathered from the EU27 via Eurostat, and other SUT and IO tables from 16 other countries.</description></item><item><title>Manual of EXIOBASE V3.8 updates</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0609/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 09:33:47 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0609/</guid><description>v3.8 was released in November 2020, provided with a full re-estimate of the time-series (to 2021) that heavily relies on &amp;ldquo;now-casting&amp;rdquo; economic structure (and environmental extensions).
The time-series extends into the future (2021), but this is based on the now-casting procedure and projections of GDP and aggregate trade of the IMF.
Main updates Macroeconomic and trade data for recent years
Updated to 2018 macroeconomic data from UN, and GDP &amp;amp; gross import/export projections until 2022 from IMF.</description></item><item><title>Impacts of COVID-19 and fiscal stimuli on global emissions and the Paris Agreement</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0528/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 11:06:53 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0528/</guid><description>Published:22 December 2020 Authors: Yuli Shan, Jiamin Ou, Daoping Wang, Zhao Zeng, Shaohui Zhang, Dabo Guan &amp; Klaus Hubacek https://www.nature.com/articles/s41558-020-00977-5
Scenarios of global lockdown and effects on CO2 emissions Economic impacts model ARIO model：Adaptive Regional Input-Output Model can be used to analyse the disaster-induced influence on regional economy.
The Leontief production function does not allow for substitution between inputs.
Scenarios of lockdown Lockdown periods Strictness of the first lockdown period Strictness of future lockdown periods Labour loss dominates the economic loss in the model.</description></item></channel></rss>