<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Environmentally Extended Input–Output Analysis on Blogs of Kai</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/categories/environmentally-extended-inputoutput-analysis/</link><description>Recent content in Environmentally Extended Input–Output Analysis on Blogs of Kai</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 11:50:18 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/categories/environmentally-extended-inputoutput-analysis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Towards a global multi-regional environmentally extended input–output database</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_220109b/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 11:50:18 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_220109b/</guid><description>&lt;p>Received 22 October 2007, &lt;strong>16 December 2008&lt;/strong>.&lt;br>
&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0921800908004801">Ecological Economics&lt;/a>&lt;br>
&lt;strong>Arnold Tukker&lt;/strong> et al. TNO, Delft, The Netherlands&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>(collection) How to connect environmental accounts to IOT</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_220109/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 09:48:54 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_220109/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Guide to OECD’sTrade in Value Added (TiVA)Indicators, 2018 edition</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0917/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 10:05:28 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0917/</guid><description>The Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development (OECD; French: Organisation de Coopération et de Développement Économiques, OCDE) is an intergovernmental economic organisation with 38 member countries.
Generally, OECD members are high-income economies with a very high Human Development Index (HDI) and are regarded as developed countries.
This guide presents the Trade in Value Added (TiVA) indicators published by OECD. The latest indicators were estimated based on the 2018 release of OECD’s annual Inter-Country Input-Output (ICIO) tables which cover the period 2005 to 2015.</description></item><item><title>Webinar: EXIOBASE 3 in SimaPro</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_09152/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 20:38:15 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_09152/</guid><description>On September 18, 2019, the developers of EXIOBASE, 2.-0 LCA Consultants, provided an overview of the database and its applications.
Covering the following topics:
Introduction to Input/Output databases and Hybrid LCAs Overview of EXIOBASE Examples of applications of EXIOBASE using SimaPro</description></item><item><title>Beggar Thy Neighbor? On the Competitiveness and Welfare Impacts of the EU’s Proposed Carbon Border Adjustment Mechanism</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0907/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 11:36:29 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0907/</guid><description>Pages Posted: 24 Jul 2021 Last revised: 30 Aug 2021
Jiarui Zhong
Martin-Luther-University Halle-Wittenberg
Jiansuo Pei
Renmin University of China - School of Applied Economics
https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=3891356
Abstract Curbing climate change is gaining increasing consensus globally. While many countries seek to set carbon prices, significant price dispersion and policy stringency continue to raise concerns about competitiveness. To address this issue, the EU has proposed a carbon border adjustment mechanism (CBAM), which aims to level the playing field by levying a carbon price on EU imports.</description></item><item><title>On the competitiveness impact of the EU CBAM: An Input-Output approach</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0826/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 10:52:33 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0826/</guid><description>Abstract While many countries seek to set a price for carbon emissions,
significant price dispersion and relative stringency keep raising concerns on carbon leakage.
We quantify the competitiveness impact of the EU CBAM based on the multi-regional Input-Output approach.</description></item><item><title>On the competitiveness impact of the EU CBAM: An Input-Output approach</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0821/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Aug 2021 16:37:59 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0821/</guid><description>Jiarui ZHONG, Martin-Luther-University, Halle-Wittenberg, Germany.
Email: Jiarui.zhong@wiwi.uni-halle.de
Jiansuo PEI (corresponding author), School of Applied Economics,
Renmin University of China, 59 Zhongguancun Street, Beijing 100872,
China, Email: jspei@ruc.edu.cn; Tel: +86-10-82500208</description></item><item><title>Global Sustainability Accounting—Developing EXIOBASE for Multi-Regional Footprint Analysis</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0719/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 09:57:38 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0719/</guid><description>A global multi-regional input−output database (EXIOBASE) with a focus on environmentally relevant activities, allowing insights into the production-related impacts and consumption footprints1.
1. Introduction 1.1. Developments in Multi-Regional Input-Output Analysis (MRIO) Harmonization Compared to other databases, EXIOBASE has a clear environmental and resource focus with high levels of detail in primary production.
Harmonizing and detailing supply and use tables (SUT):
Gathering SUT from the relevant statistical offices. In the specific case of EXIOBASE, data is gathered from the EU27 via Eurostat, and other SUT and IO tables from 16 other countries.</description></item><item><title>From Satellite to Supply Chain: New Approaches Connect Earth Observation to Economic Decisions</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0710/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 10:10:29 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0710/</guid><description>why we need more transparent supply chains? A growing share of countries’ environmental and social impacts occurs abroad; Businesses and shareholders need to identify and evaluate the potential
environmental impacts and biodiversity loss of their foreign producers; Individual consumers increasingly ask for the locations and magnitude of the impacts associated with their choices; Contributing to an accountability framework that would trigger higher environmental standards in the specific industry of producing countries.</description></item><item><title>Manual of EXIOBASE V3.8 updates</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0609/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 09:33:47 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0609/</guid><description>v3.8 was released in November 2020, provided with a full re-estimate of the time-series (to 2021) that heavily relies on &amp;ldquo;now-casting&amp;rdquo; economic structure (and environmental extensions).
The time-series extends into the future (2021), but this is based on the now-casting procedure and projections of GDP and aggregate trade of the IMF.
Main updates Macroeconomic and trade data for recent years
Updated to 2018 macroeconomic data from UN, and GDP &amp;amp; gross import/export projections until 2022 from IMF.</description></item><item><title>Linking Global Crop and Livestock Consumption to Local Production Hotspots</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0606/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 09:42:03 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0606/</guid><description>Identifying production hotspots for global crop and livestock consumption by a Spatially Explicit Multi-Reginal Input-Output model ( Zhongxiao&amp;rsquo;s work on Global Food Security).
Keywords: primary crops; animal husbandry; spatially explicit; Multi-Regional Input-Output(MRIO) analysis.
Research background Food security is challenged by increasing global food demand driven by population growth and animal-based diets. More crop production requires increasing areas of land and fresh water, causing associated environmental impacts1. Also livestock should be a focus as their feed contains harmful ingredients2 which will released to our environment finally.</description></item><item><title>Impacts of COVID-19 and fiscal stimuli on global emissions and the Paris Agreement</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0528/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 11:06:53 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0528/</guid><description>Published:22 December 2020
Authors: Yuli Shan, Jiamin Ou, Daoping Wang, Zhao Zeng, Shaohui Zhang, Dabo Guan &amp;amp; Klaus Hubacek
https://www.nature.com/articles/s41558-020-00977-5
Scenarios of global lockdown and effects on CO2 emissions Economic impacts model ARIO model：Adaptive Regional Input-Output Model can be used to analyse the disaster-induced influence on regional economy.
The Leontief production function does not allow for substitution between inputs.
Scenarios of lockdown Lockdown periods Strictness of the first lockdown period Strictness of future lockdown periods Labour loss dominates the economic loss in the model.</description></item></channel></rss>