<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Exiobase on Blogs of Kai</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/tags/exiobase/</link><description>Recent content in Exiobase on Blogs of Kai</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 20:38:15 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/tags/exiobase/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Webinar: EXIOBASE 3 in SimaPro</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_09152/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 20:38:15 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_09152/</guid><description>On September 18, 2019, the developers of EXIOBASE, 2.-0 LCA Consultants, provided an overview of the database and its applications.
Covering the following topics:
Introduction to Input/Output databases and Hybrid LCAs Overview of EXIOBASE Examples of applications of EXIOBASE using SimaPro</description></item><item><title>Global Sustainability Accounting—Developing EXIOBASE for Multi-Regional Footprint Analysis</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0719/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 09:57:38 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0719/</guid><description>A global multi-regional input−output database (EXIOBASE) with a focus on environmentally relevant activities, allowing insights into the production-related impacts and consumption footprints1.
1. Introduction 1.1. Developments in Multi-Regional Input-Output Analysis (MRIO) Harmonization Compared to other databases, EXIOBASE has a clear environmental and resource focus with high levels of detail in primary production.
Harmonizing and detailing supply and use tables (SUT):
Gathering SUT from the relevant statistical offices. In the specific case of EXIOBASE, data is gathered from the EU27 via Eurostat, and other SUT and IO tables from 16 other countries.</description></item><item><title>Manual of EXIOBASE V3.8 updates</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0609/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 09:33:47 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0609/</guid><description>v3.8 was released in November 2020, provided with a full re-estimate of the time-series (to 2021) that heavily relies on &amp;ldquo;now-casting&amp;rdquo; economic structure (and environmental extensions).
The time-series extends into the future (2021), but this is based on the now-casting procedure and projections of GDP and aggregate trade of the IMF.
Main updates Macroeconomic and trade data for recent years
Updated to 2018 macroeconomic data from UN, and GDP &amp;amp; gross import/export projections until 2022 from IMF.</description></item></channel></rss>