<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>EIOA on Blogs of Kai</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/tags/eioa/</link><description>Recent content in EIOA on Blogs of Kai</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 09:57:38 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/tags/eioa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Global Sustainability Accounting—Developing EXIOBASE for Multi-Regional Footprint Analysis</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0719/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 09:57:38 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0719/</guid><description>A global multi-regional input−output database (EXIOBASE) with a focus on environmentally relevant activities, allowing insights into the production-related impacts and consumption footprints1.
1. Introduction 1.1. Developments in Multi-Regional Input-Output Analysis (MRIO) Harmonization Compared to other databases, EXIOBASE has a clear environmental and resource focus with high levels of detail in primary production.
Harmonizing and detailing supply and use tables (SUT):
Gathering SUT from the relevant statistical offices. In the specific case of EXIOBASE, data is gathered from the EU27 via Eurostat, and other SUT and IO tables from 16 other countries.</description></item><item><title>GIA in the EIOA class: exploring the impact of Brexit (2)</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_iga_06072/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 15:35:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_iga_06072/</guid><description>The Brexit topic from the BBC News.
(The Brexit topic link/Group drive)
Scenario analysis source: Assessing energy and economic impacts of large-scale policy shocks based on Input-Output analysis: Application to Brexit
Research background from the latest Brexit News Farmers should not fear Australia trade deal, UK minister says 27/05/2021 Keywords: free trade deal with Au; competition of UK farmers; gateway to TPP.
Farmers have warned they could struggle to compete if Australia was given tariff-free access to UK markets.</description></item><item><title>GIA in the EIOA class: exploring the impact of Brexit (1)</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0607/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 15:34:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_0607/</guid><description>UK companies can and should see the current high-uncertainty environment as a spur to rethink their supply chain strategies and make them more resilient. https://www.mckinsey.com/featured-insights/europe/brexit-the-bigger-picture-rethinking-supply-chains-in-a-time-of-uncertainty
Why Europe is so critical in British supply chains The EU is the UK&amp;rsquo;s largest trading partner, accounting for approximately half of both imports and exports of goods (Exhibit1). Moreover, a large proportion of the UK’s imports from and exports to the EU are in the form of intermediary products—an indicator of the high degree of interconnectedness between UK and EU supply chains (Exhibit 2).</description></item><item><title>Impacts of COVID-19 and fiscal stimuli on global emissions and the Paris Agreement</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0528/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 11:06:53 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0528/</guid><description>Published:22 December 2020 Authors: Yuli Shan, Jiamin Ou, Daoping Wang, Zhao Zeng, Shaohui Zhang, Dabo Guan &amp; Klaus Hubacek https://www.nature.com/articles/s41558-020-00977-5
Scenarios of global lockdown and effects on CO2 emissions Economic impacts model ARIO model：Adaptive Regional Input-Output Model can be used to analyse the disaster-induced influence on regional economy.
The Leontief production function does not allow for substitution between inputs.
Scenarios of lockdown Lockdown periods Strictness of the first lockdown period Strictness of future lockdown periods Labour loss dominates the economic loss in the model.</description></item><item><title>EIOA Class: Integrated Group Assignment(IGA)</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_05173/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/skill_05173/</guid><description>&lt;p>Each group is expected to perform a research question about two real-world issues: BREXIT and national stimulus plans.
in a post COVID-19 world.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>