<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>LCA on Blogs of Kai</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/tags/lca/</link><description>Recent content in LCA on Blogs of Kai</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2021 22:00:18 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/tags/lca/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Emerging role of Geographical Information System (GIS), Life Cycle Assessment (LCA) and spatial LCA (GIS-LCA) in sustainable bioenergy planning</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0822/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2021 22:00:18 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0822/</guid><description>https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0960852417303516#f0010
Abstract Sustainability of a bioenergy project depends on precise assessment of biomass resource, planning of cost-effective logistics and evaluation of possible environmental implications. In this context, this paper reviews the role and applications of geo-spatial tool such as Geographical Information System (GIS) for precise agro-residue resource assessment, biomass logistic and power plant design. Further, application of Life Cycle Assessment (LCA) in understanding the potential impact of agro-residue bioenergy generation on different ecosystem services has also been reviewed and limitations associated with LCA variability and uncertainty were discussed.</description></item><item><title>LC-IMPACT: A regionalized life cycle damage assessment method</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0818/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 12:19:10 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0818/</guid><description>https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1111/jiec.13018
Abstract Here, we present the LC-IMPACT method that provides characterization factors at the damage level for 11 impact categories related to three areas of protection (human health, ecosystem quality, natural resources).</description></item><item><title>Advanced Course on LCA —— Session 3: Economic Allocation</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0816/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 16:13:31 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0816/</guid><description>Session 3 Purpose This software session focuses on reproducing the results of an LCA paper on economic allocation, defining functional flows and identifying multi functional processes, with the software program CMLCA. In today’s exercises, you will learn:
to understand the main principles of economic allocation; how such analyses work in CMLCA software. You may perform the exercise alone or together with (a) colleague(s) in a virtual room, and again, you don’t have to hand in the results.</description></item><item><title>Economic Allocation: Examples and Derived Decision Tree</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0815/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 09:24:52 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0815/</guid><description>https://link.springer.com/content/pdf/10.1007/BF02978533.pdf
Economic Allocation: Examples and Derived Decision Tree Jeroen B. Guinde*, Reinout Heijungs and Gjah Huppes Institute of Environmental Sciences (CML), Leiden University, P.O. Box 9518, 2300 RA Leiden, The Netherlands Int J LCA 9 (1) 23 - 33 (2004)
Abstract Goal, Scope and Background. In the recently published (Dutch) Handbook on LCA, economic allocation is advised as baseline method for most allocation situations in a detailed LCA. Although the Handbook on LCA aimed to provide a &amp;lsquo;cookbook&amp;rsquo; with operational guidelines for conducting each step of an LCA, this was not completely achieved for the allocation step.</description></item><item><title>Proper or messy allocation?--Systematic approach to identifying and solving multi-functionality in LCA</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0814/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2021 11:20:07 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0814/</guid><description>Avoided burden1 Most existing LCA databases today do not include multi-functional processes.
including ecoinvent MF is &amp;lsquo;solved&amp;rsquo; by database developers by delivering only mono-functional datasets.
Mostly, practitioners cannot change this methodological decision anymore and often don&amp;rsquo;t realize that they are handling (&amp;lsquo;accepting&amp;rsquo;) more MF issues than they realize.
Consequently, most software doesn&amp;rsquo;t include ways to address MF.
While it is known as one of the most determining factors of LCA results.</description></item><item><title>Land use indicators in LCA</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_rp_0810/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 09:54:21 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_rp_0810/</guid><description>Principles for life cycle inventories of land use on a global scale Thomas Koellner, Laura de Baan, Tabea Beck, Miguel Brandão, Barbara Civit, Mark Goedkoop, Manuele Margni, Llorenç Milà i Canals, Ruedi Müller-Wenk, Bo Weidema &amp;amp; Bastian Wittstock The International Journal of Life Cycle Assessment volume 18, pages1203–1215 (2013) https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s11367-012-0392-0
Land use elementary flows In LCA, land occupation and land transformation can be distinguished as basic types of land use elementary flows (Milà i Canals et al.</description></item><item><title>Literature review on the land use of future energy</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0809/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 11:26:59 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0809/</guid><description>https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S1364032108001354
Land use and electricity generation: A life-cycle analysis Renewable and Sustainable Energy Reviews Volume 13, Issues 6–7, August–September 2009, Pages 1465-1474
Vasilis Fthenakis¹, Hyung Chul Kim² ¹ National Photovoltaic Environmental Research Center, Brookhaven National Laboratory, Bldg 475B, Upton, NY 11973, United States ² Center for Life Cycle Analysis, Columbia University, New York, NY 10027, United States
Abstract Renewable-energy sources often are regarded as dispersed and difficult to collect, thus requiring substantial land resources in comparison to conventional energy sources.</description></item><item><title>Waste is not a service</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0808/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2021 11:03:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0808/</guid><description>https://link.springer.com/content/pdf/10.1007/s11367-021-01955-5.pdf
Almost every overview of LCA gives a graphical indication of the idea of a life cycle. Such diagrams consist of a linear sequence or network of blocks, connected with arrows, representing the major life stages of a product life cycle. Examples from recent textbooks on LCA can be found in Klöpffer and Grahl (2014, p. 2), Jolliet et al. (2016, p. 36), and Hauschild et al. (2018, p. 120). All such flow diagrams agree on the basic setup of a chronological order: resource becomes products, products are used, and it all ends with disposal of waste.</description></item><item><title>Spatially-explicit footprints of agricultural commodities Mapping carbon emissions embodied in Brazil's soy exports</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0706/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 17:08:59 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0706/</guid><description>Abstract LCA faces limitations when it comes to addressing spatial and temporal variability in production, transportation and manufacturing systems. By the integration of LCA principles with enhanced physical trade flow analysis. Estimating the carbon footprint1 of Brazilian soy exports over the period 2010–2015 based on over 90000 individual traded flows of beans, oil and protein cake from the municipality of origin through international markets. A large spatial variability in co2 across sourcing areas, importers and sub-stages has been detected.</description></item></channel></rss>