<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>LCA on Blogs of Kai</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/tags/lca/</link><description>Recent content in LCA on Blogs of Kai</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 15:00:38 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/tags/lca/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Environmental life cycle cost assessment: Recycling of hard plastic waste collected at Danish recycling centres</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/pl/lca_reccost/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 15:00:38 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/pl/lca_reccost/</guid><description/></item><item><title>(Collection) life cycle cost assessment of plastic waste</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/pl/co_lcaccost/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 16:26:15 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/pl/co_lcaccost/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Life Cycle Assessment (LCA) of alternative feedstocks for plastics production</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/pl/rp_lcaplaspro/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 10:23:35 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/pl/rp_lcaplaspro/</guid><description>&lt;p>the Joint Research Centre (JRC)&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>(Collection) LCA of plastic or packaging waste</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/pl/co_1214_lca/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 11:17:02 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/pl/co_1214_lca/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Emerging role of Geographical Information System (GIS), Life Cycle Assessment (LCA) and spatial LCA (GIS-LCA) in sustainable bioenergy planning</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/lca_gis/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2021 22:00:18 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/lca_gis/</guid><description>https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0960852417303516#f0010
Abstract Sustainability of a bioenergy project depends on precise assessment of biomass resource, planning of cost-effective logistics and evaluation of possible environmental implications. In this context, this paper reviews the role and applications of geo-spatial tool such as Geographical Information System (GIS) for precise agro-residue resource assessment, biomass logistic and power plant design. Further, application of Life Cycle Assessment (LCA) in understanding the potential impact of agro-residue bioenergy generation on different ecosystem services has also been reviewed and limitations associated with LCA variability and uncertainty were discussed.</description></item><item><title>LC-IMPACT: A regionalized life cycle damage assessment method</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/re_0818/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 12:19:10 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/re_0818/</guid><description>https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1111/jiec.13018
Abstract Here, we present the LC-IMPACT method that provides characterization factors at the damage level for 11 impact categories related to three areas of protection (human health, ecosystem quality, natural resources).</description></item><item><title>Land use indicators in LCA</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/re_0810/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 09:54:21 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/re_0810/</guid><description>Principles for life cycle inventories of land use on a global scale Thomas Koellner, Laura de Baan, Tabea Beck, Miguel Brandão, Barbara Civit, Mark Goedkoop, Manuele Margni, Llorenç Milà i Canals, Ruedi Müller-Wenk, Bo Weidema &amp;amp; Bastian Wittstock
The International Journal of Life Cycle Assessment volume 18, pages1203–1215 (2013)
https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s11367-012-0392-0
Land use elementary flows In LCA, land occupation and land transformation can be distinguished as basic types of land use elementary flows (Milà i Canals et al.</description></item><item><title>Literature review on the land use of future energy</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/re_0809/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 11:26:59 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/re_0809/</guid><description>https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S1364032108001354
Land use and electricity generation: A life-cycle analysis Renewable and Sustainable Energy Reviews
Volume 13, Issues 6–7, August–September 2009, Pages 1465-1474
Vasilis Fthenakis¹, Hyung Chul Kim²
¹ National Photovoltaic Environmental Research Center, Brookhaven National Laboratory, Bldg 475B, Upton, NY 11973, United States
² Center for Life Cycle Analysis, Columbia University, New York, NY 10027, United States
Abstract Renewable-energy sources often are regarded as dispersed and difficult to collect, thus requiring substantial land resources in comparison to conventional energy sources.</description></item><item><title>Spatially-explicit footprints of agricultural commodities Mapping carbon emissions embodied in Brazil's soy exports</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/re_0706/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 17:08:59 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/re_0706/</guid><description>Abstract LCA faces limitations when it comes to addressing spatial and temporal variability in production, transportation and manufacturing systems. By the integration of LCA principles with enhanced physical trade flow analysis. Estimating the carbon footprint1 of Brazilian soy exports over the period 2010–2015 based on over 90000 individual traded flows of beans, oil and protein cake from the municipality of origin through international markets. A large spatial variability in co2 across sourcing areas, importers and sub-stages has been detected.</description></item></channel></rss>