<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Food on Blogs of Kai</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/categories/food/</link><description>Recent content in Food on Blogs of Kai</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 21:47:53 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/categories/food/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What is the healthiest way to cook vegetables to maximize their nutritional value?</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_1025/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 21:47:53 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_1025/</guid><description>&lt;p>Vegetables lose some nutritional value in transportation, so when possible, buy produce from farmers’ markets.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Is beer better (or worse) for you than wine?</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0627/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 23:34:41 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0627/</guid><description>Few drinks (save tea or coffee) divide the world so spectacularly as beer or wine. There’s no accounting for taste, of course – but there are subtle differences in the way they affect your body and determine your health. Is one more fattening than another? How do their heart benefits compare? And which gives the worse hangover?
BBC Future has combed through the data to bust some of the myths surrounding two of the world’s favourite drinks.</description></item><item><title>What you should know about beer?</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0626/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 21:50:46 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0626/</guid><description>BEER: WHERE DO ALL THOSE FLAVOURS COME FROM? There are thousands of different ways that yeast, malt, and hops that can be combined to make beer, and all those combinations can lead to lots of interesting outcomes. There are also a LOT of additives you can put in beer to give it different flavours, but I’m going to focus on the core ingredients: yeast, hops, and malt.
Yeast Yeast is a fungus.</description></item><item><title>All about the lettuce</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0602/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 18:46:44 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/de_0602/</guid><description>&amp;lsquo;Leaf lettuce, head lettuce, green lettuce, red lettuce….who knew there were so many kinds of lettuce? This is your handy guide to knowing what kind of lettuce your are eating with.&amp;rsquo;
Types of Lettuce Iceberg Butterhead Romaine Leaf Kale ICEBERG LETTUCE This is probably the most famous and recognizable form of head lettuce. Iceberg lettuce is also sometimes referred to as crisphead, and it is a pale green leafy vegetable that forms into a tight cabbage style head.</description></item></channel></rss>