<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>research proposal on Blogs of Kai</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/tags/research-proposal/</link><description>Recent content in research proposal on Blogs of Kai</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 09:54:21 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/tags/research-proposal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Land use indicators in LCA</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0810/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 09:54:21 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0810/</guid><description>Principles for life cycle inventories of land use on a global scale Thomas Koellner, Laura de Baan, Tabea Beck, Miguel Brandão, Barbara Civit, Mark Goedkoop, Manuele Margni, Llorenç Milà i Canals, Ruedi Müller-Wenk, Bo Weidema &amp;amp; Bastian Wittstock
The International Journal of Life Cycle Assessment volume 18, pages1203–1215 (2013)
https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s11367-012-0392-0
Land use elementary flows In LCA, land occupation and land transformation can be distinguished as basic types of land use elementary flows (Milà i Canals et al.</description></item><item><title>Assessing the spatially explicit global footprints of European net-zero strategies</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0602/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 10:11:09 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0602/</guid><description>“Someone’s sitting in the shade today because someone planted a tree a long time ago” &amp;mdash;Warren Buffett.
Research aim Building a detailed, spatially explicit, internationally trade linked GMRIO of food and energy systems at a ~5arc min(9km) resolution. Exploring current environmental and social footprints of these systems and the threats or opportunities presented by EU net-zero strategies. Incorporating net-zero pathways from the literature into the model from both production and consumption perspectives, and connecting land suitability maps for future renewable energy, mining, and agriculture potentials.</description></item><item><title>RP Project</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0526/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 10:10:16 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0526/</guid><description>Measuring in Arc-Seconds The source link
USGS: United States Geological Survey. DEM: Digital elevation model [Wiki search](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Digital_elevation_model#:~:text=A%20digital%20elevation%20model%20(DEM,to%20a%20discrete%20global%20grid) Some USGS DEM data is stored in a format that utilizes three, five, or 30 arc-seconds of longitude and latitude to register cell values. The geographic reference system treats the globe as if it were a sphere divided into 360 equal parts called degrees.
Said differently, an arc-second represents the distance of latitude or longitude across the earth&amp;rsquo;s surface with the angle of one second.</description></item></channel></rss>