<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Material Flow Analysis on Blogs of Kai</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/categories/material-flow-analysis/</link><description>Recent content in Material Flow Analysis on Blogs of Kai</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 20:48:15 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/categories/material-flow-analysis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Building stock energy modeling considering building system composition and long-term change for climate change mitigation of commercial building stocks</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_11042/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 20:48:15 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_11042/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Global construction materials database and stock analysis of residential buildings between 1970-2050</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_1104/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 09:47:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_1104/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Modelling global material stocks and flows for residential and service sector buildings towards 2050</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_1102/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 10:04:18 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_1102/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Global Scenarios of Resource and Emissions Savings from systemic Material Efficiency in Buildings and Cars</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0521/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 11:12:40 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0521/</guid><description>Abstract Here we present a high-resolution approach for tracking material flows and energy use of products throughout their life cycles, focusing on passenger vehicles and residential buildings. We estimate future changes in material flows and operational energy use due to increased yields, light-weight designs, material substitution, increased service efficiency, extended service life, and increased reuse and recycling.
Main Text comprised of 20 countries/regions six major climate-relevant materials (aluminium, cement, copper, plastics, steel, wood) for the period 2016 - 2060.</description></item></channel></rss>