<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>OECD on Blogs of Kai</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/tags/oecd/</link><description>Recent content in OECD on Blogs of Kai</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 19:45:49 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/tags/oecd/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>OECD Expert workshop on Economic Modelling of Climate and Related Tipping Points</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/econ_tippingp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 19:45:49 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/econ_tippingp/</guid><description>&lt;p>Emerging evidence highlights the increasing risks of &lt;em>&lt;strong>non-linearities and systemic changes caused by climate change&lt;/strong>&lt;/em>. These include large-scale tipping points in the earth’s climate such as the disintegration of the Greenland and West Antarctic Ice Sheets, permafrost collapse, and the breakdown of the Atlantic Meridional Overturning Circulation among others.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Guide to OECD’sTrade in Value Added (TiVA) Indicators, 2018 edition</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/econ_valueadded/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 10:05:28 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re/econ_valueadded/</guid><description>The Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development (OECD; French: Organisation de Coopération et de Développement Économiques, OCDE) is an intergovernmental economic organisation with 38 member countries.
Generally, OECD members are high-income economies with a very high Human Development Index (HDI) and are regarded as developed countries.
This guide presents the Trade in Value Added (TiVA) indicators published by OECD. The latest indicators were estimated based on the 2018 release of OECD’s annual Inter-Country Input-Output (ICIO) tables which cover the period 2005 to 2015.</description></item></channel></rss>