<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>EEIOA on Blogs of Kai</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/tags/eeioa/</link><description>Recent content in EEIOA on Blogs of Kai</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 10:10:29 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/tags/eeioa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>From Satellite to Supply Chain: New Approaches Connect Earth Observation to Economic Decisions</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0710/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 10:10:29 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0710/</guid><description>why we need more transparent supply chains? A growing share of countries’ environmental and social impacts occurs abroad; Businesses and shareholders need to identify and evaluate the potential
environmental impacts and biodiversity loss of their foreign producers; Individual consumers increasingly ask for the locations and magnitude of the impacts associated with their choices; Contributing to an accountability framework that would trigger higher environmental standards in the specific industry of producing countries.</description></item><item><title>Manual of EXIOBASE V3.8 updates</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0609/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 09:33:47 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0609/</guid><description>v3.8 was released in November 2020, provided with a full re-estimate of the time-series (to 2021) that heavily relies on &amp;ldquo;now-casting&amp;rdquo; economic structure (and environmental extensions).
The time-series extends into the future (2021), but this is based on the now-casting procedure and projections of GDP and aggregate trade of the IMF.
Main updates Macroeconomic and trade data for recent years
Updated to 2018 macroeconomic data from UN, and GDP &amp;amp; gross import/export projections until 2022 from IMF.</description></item><item><title>Linking Global Crop and Livestock Consumption to Local Production Hotspots</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0606/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 09:42:03 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0606/</guid><description>Identifying production hotspots for global crop and livestock consumption by a Spatially Explicit Multi-Reginal Input-Output model ( Zhongxiao&amp;rsquo;s work on Global Food Security).
Keywords: primary crops; animal husbandry; spatially explicit; Multi-Regional Input-Output(MRIO) analysis.
Research background Food security is challenged by increasing global food demand driven by population growth and animal-based diets. More crop production requires increasing areas of land and fresh water, causing associated environmental impacts1. Also livestock should be a focus as their feed contains harmful ingredients2 which will released to our environment finally.</description></item><item><title>Impacts of COVID-19 and fiscal stimuli on global emissions and the Paris Agreement</title><link>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0528/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 11:06:53 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xiaoshan1994.github.io/post/re_0528/</guid><description>Published:22 December 2020
Authors: Yuli Shan, Jiamin Ou, Daoping Wang, Zhao Zeng, Shaohui Zhang, Dabo Guan &amp;amp; Klaus Hubacek
https://www.nature.com/articles/s41558-020-00977-5
Scenarios of global lockdown and effects on CO2 emissions Economic impacts model ARIO model：Adaptive Regional Input-Output Model can be used to analyse the disaster-induced influence on regional economy.
The Leontief production function does not allow for substitution between inputs.
Scenarios of lockdown Lockdown periods Strictness of the first lockdown period Strictness of future lockdown periods Labour loss dominates the economic loss in the model.</description></item></channel></rss>